<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" media="screen" href="/~d/styles/rss2full.xsl"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" media="screen" href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~d/styles/itemcontent.css"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:taxo="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/taxonomy/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:feedburner="http://rssnamespace.org/feedburner/ext/1.0" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Android Central - Android Forums, News, Reviews, Help and Android Wallpapers</title>
    <link>http://www.androidcentral.com/</link>
    <description>Android Central</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 01:57:24 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 01:57:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>30</ttl>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/androidcentral" />
    <feedburner:info uri="androidcentral" />
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="hub" href="http://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/" />
    <feedburner:emailServiceId>androidcentral</feedburner:emailServiceId>
    <feedburner:feedburnerHostname>https://feedburner.google.com</feedburner:feedburnerHostname>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking your Chromebook is fun and easier than you think</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/ITsohKXZpyM/story01.htm</link>
      <description>It's easy to make your Chromebook more than the sum of its parts. A Chromebook can be a great purchase even if you never step outside of Google's trusted environment. They are some of the best web machines ever built, require almost no software maintenance, and come in a myriad of different styles and price points. We love the things, and the numbers say we're not alone. But like anything electronic, sometimes it's fun to push the envelope and do things a little outside of the intended use. Sometimes that means hidden features in the software, sometimes it means altering the software, and sometimes it means replacing the software entirely. We're familiar with people doing just that with Android, but it's also pretty easy to do with your Chromebook. The best part is that it's also very easy to go back. Let's have a look at what you need to get started, and where to begin. Create a recovery image Before you start doing anything it's always a good idea to have a path back to a ...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 01:49:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40322 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"><div class="field-items"><div class="field-item even"><p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/hacking-your-chromebook-fun-and-easier-you-think' title="Hacking your Chromebook is fun and easier than you think"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2014/08/Chromebook-hacking-6.jpg?itok=y5WagJCZ' /></a></p> <p class="intro">It's easy to make your Chromebook more than the sum of its parts.</p> <p>A <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/chromebook">Chromebook</a> can be a great purchase even if you never step outside of Google's trusted environment. They are some of the best web machines ever built, require almost no software maintenance, and come in a myriad of different styles and price points. We love the things, and the numbers say <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/la-schools-offer-students-hybrids-laptops-instead-apple-ipads">we're not alone</a>.</p> <p>But like anything electronic, sometimes it's fun to <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/tag/hacking">push the envelope</a> and do things a little outside of the intended use. Sometimes that means hidden features in the software, sometimes it means altering the software, and sometimes it means replacing the software entirely. We're familiar with people doing just that with Android, but it's also pretty easy to do with your Chromebook. The best part is that it's also very easy to go back.</p> <p>Let's have a look at what you need to get started, and where to begin.</p> <!--break--> <h2>Create a recovery image</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/hacking-your-chromebook-fun-and-easier-you-think' title="Hacking your Chromebook is fun and easier than you think"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2014/08/Chromebook-hacking-2.jpg?itok=5ZzCl6sM' /></a></p> <p>Before you start doing anything it's always a good idea to have a path back to a time when everything worked. Luckily, that's fairly easy when we're talking about a Chromebook.</p> <p>Google has an official tool that will install the factory-issued software to your Chrome device on a 4GB or larger USB stick or SD card. You can then use this media to restore your Chromebook just like it was fresh out of the box.</p> <p>Google has <a href="https://support.google.com/chromebook/answer/1080595?hl=en">full instructions on using their tool here</a> but here's the process in a nutshell:</p> <ol><li>Insert the media you'll be using as a recovery disk into a Windows, OS X or Linux computer that you have admin rights on.</li> <li>Install the correct version of the recovery tool for your platform via the links at Google's site.</li> <li>Run the recovery tool and tell it which Chrome device you're building a restore image for.</li> <li>When you're finished, use the media you created to restore your Chromebook from recovery mode. <a href="https://support.google.com/chromebook/answer/1080595">Full instructions for the various models are right here</a>.</li> </ol><p>Reboot and enjoy your factory-fresh software!</p> <h2>Change to the beta or dev channel</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/hacking-your-chromebook-fun-and-easier-you-think' title="Hacking your Chromebook is fun and easier than you think"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brb/public/article_images/2014/08/Chromebook-hacking-3.jpg?itok=qftt2yqD' /></a></p> <p>This is really simple and something I recommend. By default, your Chromebook runs on the stable release channel for your model. This means everything has been tested, things run pretty smoothly, and there usually aren't any critical bugs to trip you up.</p> <p>That's absolutely no fun.</p> <p>The good news is that we all can be testers by switching the software channel in the settings. Click the Chrome OS wrench icon in the lower right and open the settings. Choose About Chrome OS &gt; More Info. Click the Change Channel button and choose between Stable, Beta and Dev - Unstable channels in the popover window that appears.</p> <p>Both the beta and the dev channel give you access to upcoming (both default and experimental settings — see below) features that aren't in the stable channel just yet. I've always found the beta channel to work pretty well, but expect issues and glitches on the dev channel along with the latest features.</p> <p>If you just want everything to work, switching back to the stable channel is just as easy — choose it from the same list!</p> <h2>Tweaking the settings</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/hacking-your-chromebook-fun-and-easier-you-think' title="Hacking your Chromebook is fun and easier than you think"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brb/public/article_images/2014/08/Chromebook-hacking-4.jpg?itok=th-rPcs5' /></a></p> <p>Chrome — both the operating system and the stand alone browser for Windows Mac and Linux — has an entire page filled with "experimental" settings. Some will absolutely break things, others might improve your experience. Find them is simple.</p> <p>Fire up the browser and enter <em>chrome://flags</em> into the Omnibox (a fancy name for the URL bar in Chrome) then hit enter.</p> <p>You'll be faced with a huge list of features that you can enable or disable at will. All of them are experimental, some are serious security holes, others are potential <em>oh-crap-I-need-to-reload-EVERYTHING</em> bringers of doom. We don't recommend you just jump in and start enabling things. Instead, <a href="http://forums.androidcentral.com/chrome-os/">talk to people</a> who are using the same model of Chromebook that you are and find out what works and what doesn't.</p> <p>It's also worth remembering that these experimental flags can disappear at any time. Some may be merged into the OS, others will just up and disappear. If you do enable something, lets say for example, GPU compositing, and it breaks everything (yeah, I've been there), you have your recovery media you made earlier to save your bacon.</p> <h2>Install Linux</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/hacking-your-chromebook-fun-and-easier-you-think' title="Hacking your Chromebook is fun and easier than you think"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2014/08/Chromebook-hacking-5.jpg?itok=jHAELA2n' /></a></p> <p>One of those complicated things that has been made simple by the work of great developers, <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/chromebook-pixel-might-be-new-linux-ultrabook-you-re-waiting">installing Linux on your Chromebook</a> is a great way expand its capabilities. Chrome OS <em>is</em> a flavor of Linux, but it's been trimmed down and many features have been removed. We're going to look at the simple (and in my opinion the best) way to build a dual-boot environment so you have both Chrome OS and <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/ubuntu">Ubuntu</a> LTS using <em>David Schneider's</em> excellent tool called crouton (Chromium OS Universal Chroot Environment).</p> <p>You'll need to enable developer mode on your Chromebook, and the method varies from device to device. You may need to flip a hidden switch, or enter a key combination during boot. You can find exactly how to enable developer mode for your Chromebook on Google, and once you've done that everything else is the same no matter which model you use.</p> <p>Once you're a developer (or at least in dev mode) you'll need to head to the <a href="https://github.com/dnschneid/crouton">crouton project page at github</a> and download the script from the top of the page. Save it to your Downloads folder and you're ready to get started.</p> <p>Open a terminal (I told you Chrome OS was Linux) by pressing Ctrl+Alt+T and enter the word <em>shell</em> to open a shell.</p> <p>Next, run crouton to see all the help text and examples like this:</p> <blockquote> <p><em>sh -e ~/Downloads/crouton</em></p> </blockquote> <p>Read everything you find there, as these are your options and tell crouton what to install. If you don't understand an option, ask someone. Also, read the help section at the crouton github page for examples and hints.</p> <p>Once you have crouton set up, you'll be able to swap between Chrome OS and a full fledged install of Linux (Ubuntu LTS) at will.</p> <p>While I like the flexibility of having both Chrome OS and Ubuntu on the same machine, you may want to be rid of Chrome OS completely. If you're interested in <em>replacing</em> Chrome OS with Ubuntu, have a look at the <a href="http://chromeos-cr48.blogspot.fr/">ChrUbuntu project here</a>. If you want to replace Chrome OS on your Pixel with Debian Wheezy, grab a beverage and <a href="http://grephaxs.com/chromebook-install-debian-on-chromebook-with-crouton/">have a look here</a>.</p> <h2>Building Chromium yourself</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/hacking-your-chromebook-fun-and-easier-you-think' title="Hacking your Chromebook is fun and easier than you think"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2014/08/Chromium-github.png?itok=qiDq2kr3' /></a></p> <p>If you're an advanced user, or want to tackle an ambitious project with the ultimate Chromey reward, you can build Chromium yourself for your Chromebook.</p> <p>This isn't all that difficult if you're familiar with building a big software project, but it can be pretty daunting for a first-timer. Everything you need to know is at the <a href="http://www.chromium.org/chromium-os/how-tos-and-troubleshooting/building-chromium-browser">Chromium Project</a> pages but it breaks down into a few basic steps:</p> <ul><li>Download a local copy of the <a href="http://www.chromium.org/developers/how-tos/get-the-code">Chromium source code</a> </li> <li>Download and install a local copy of the <a href="http://www.chromium.org/developers/how-tos/install-depot-tools">required build tools</a></li> <li>Build and install the software</li> </ul><p>Everything is documented and if you can follow directions you <em>should</em> be able to build and install Chromium with any Windows, Linux or Mac computer. Just like <a href="http://forums.androidcentral.com/general-help-how/144804-how-compile-ics-aosp-4-0-3-xoom-gnex-nexus-s.html">building Android yourself</a>, this allows you to customize just about anything you can think of before you build it. And just like building Android, if you don't make any changes you have the same basic system you would have if someone else did the building and you just installed it. Building Chromium is an excellent way to learn a few things and see how the process works, but don't expect software made of miracles and unicorns when you're done.</p> <hr /><p>These are just a few of the neat hackery tricks you can do with your new Chromebook. And like everything else, it may turn out that none of it is for you and you prefer things that just work as intended. That's cool, and sometimes when I'm staring at the screen of a device that won't boot, I'm right there with ya.</p> <p>If you do want to dive in and have a go at Chrome OS, this is how I do it. Tell me how <em>you</em> do it in the comments, I'd love to hear about it!</p> </div></div></div><br clear='all'/><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/a2.htm"><img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/a2.img" border="0"/></a><img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386677395/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/a2t.img" border="0"/><img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/mf.gif' border='0'/><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/ITsohKXZpyM" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Jerry Hildenbrand</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb760fd/sc/15/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Chacking0Eyour0Echromebook0Efun0Eand0Eeasier0Eyou0Ethink/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The top phones you need to know, by manufacturer</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/ccVBg_XJG0g/story01.htm</link>
      <description>How many different Android phones do you think are out there? Chances are whatever you guessed is low. We're talking thousands of models from more manufacturers than we care to count. So we don't blame if you if you're new to the smartphone game and feel a little overwhelmed. It's a big, big Android world out there. But we're going to make it a little easier on you. We've broken down the top Android smartphones you need to know by the world's top manufacturers. This isn't an all-inclusive list. It's not even a list of that we think "the best" is. (That list lives here, and it's definitely open to debate.) No, this is a list to help you get started. These are the phones we'd tell you to look at if you asked us what's good from a particular manufacturer. We'll continue to add and remove phones as new ones are announced and older ones age out. The top phones from HTCThe top phones from HuaweiThe top phones from LGThe top phones from MotorolaThe top phones from SamsungThe top phones...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 00:24:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44433 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"><div class="field-items"><div class="field-item even"><p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-android-phone-by-manufacturer' title="The top phones you need to know, by manufacturer"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2015/11/pile-of-phones-nov-2015.jpg?itok=vMLWRRHx' /></a></p> <p>How many different Android phones do you think are out there? Chances are whatever you guessed is low. We're talking thousands of models from more manufacturers than we care to count. So we don't blame if you if you're new to the smartphone game and feel a little overwhelmed. It's a big, big Android world out there.</p> <p>But we're going to make it a little easier on you. We've broken down the top Android smartphones you need to know by the world's top manufacturers. This isn't an all-inclusive list. It's not even a list of that we think "the best" is. (<a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/best-android-phones">That list lives here</a>, and it's definitely open to debate.)</p> <p>No, this is a list to help you get started. These are the phones we'd tell you to look at if you asked us what's good from a particular manufacturer. We'll continue to add and remove phones as new ones are announced and older ones age out.</p> <!--break--> <p><a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/these-are-htc-phones-you-need-know" title="" class="cta large">The top phones from HTC</a><br /><a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/these-are-top-huawei-phones-you-need-know" title="" class="cta large">The top phones from Huawei</a><br /><a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/these-are-top-lg-phones-you-need-know" title="" class="cta large">The top phones from LG</a><br /><a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/these-are-top-motorola-phones-you-need-know" title="" class="cta large">The top phones from Motorola</a><br /><a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/these-are-top-samsung-phones-you-need-know" title="" class="cta large">The top phones from Samsung</a><br /><a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/these-are-top-sony-xperia-phones-you-need-know" title="" class="cta large">The top phones from Sony</a> <br /><a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/these-are-top-xiaomi-phones-you-need-know" title="" class="cta large">The top phones from Xiaomi</a><br /><a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/these-are-top-asus-phones-you-need-know" title="" class="cta large">The top phones from ASUS</a></p> <p>We've still got a few more manufacturers to add in here, so check back if you haven't found what you're looking for.</p> </div></div></div><br clear='all'/><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/a2.htm"><img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/a2.img" border="0"/></a><img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386676212/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/a2t.img" border="0"/><img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/mf.gif' border='0'/><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/ccVBg_XJG0g" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Phil Nickinson</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb75bcb/sc/15/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Cbest0Eandroid0Ephone0Eby0Emanufacturer/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Auto update removes interaction limit on Google Play Music when your car is parked</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/fef51qnTojA/story01.htm</link>
      <description>Android Auto, since launch, has always limited user interactions with the screen to just six taps. That is, until today, when an Android Auto app update made a big improvement by letting you interact with your Google Play Music as much as you want ... so long as your car is parked. After being alerted to the improvement by Ryan Warner over on Twitter, we've confirmed on our end that the latest update does indeed remove the interaction restriction. If your car is parked, you can tap and scroll all you want through Google Play Music without any lockouts. What we can't say at this point is how this will be handled on other apps. Seeing this change shows it's indeed possible to have an app behave differently when the car is parked versus being driven — which makes sense based on how lots of car infotainment systems operate — but seeing this change only for Google Play Music at this point is a bit odd. If Google is indeed easing this interaction limit when the car is parked across...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 23:52:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53444 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded>&lt;div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"&gt;&lt;div class="field-items"&gt;&lt;div class="field-item even"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/google-play-music-update-android-auto-removes-interaction-limit-when-your-car-parked' title="Android Auto update removes interaction limit on Google Play Music when your car is parked"&gt;&lt;img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2015/08/android-auto-overview-update.jpg?itok=5DmM-3Fh' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./android-auto"&gt;Android Auto&lt;/a&gt;, since launch, has always &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/why-one-well-intentioned-android-auto-safety-feature-may-be-moot"&gt;limited user interactions with the screen&lt;/a&gt; to just six taps. That is, until today, when an &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/android-auto-expands-18-new-countries"&gt;Android Auto app update&lt;/a&gt; made a big improvement by letting you interact with your Google Play Music as much as you want ... so long as your car is parked. &lt;!--break--&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;After being alerted to the improvement &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/rwarner/status/717093763424890882"&gt;by Ryan Warner over on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, we've confirmed on our end that the latest update does indeed remove the interaction restriction. If your car is parked, you can tap and scroll all you want through Google Play Music without any lockouts.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What we can't say at this point is how this will be handled on other apps. Seeing this change shows it's indeed possible to have an app behave differently when the car is parked versus being driven — which makes sense based on how &lt;em&gt;lots&lt;/em&gt; of car infotainment systems operate — but seeing this change &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; for Google Play Music at this point is a bit odd.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If Google is indeed easing this interaction limit when the car is parked across the board, it seems like app developers will have to update things slightly in their own apps to take advantage of the change in restrictions on Google's end. If that's the case, we should see the fruits of this change soon.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="devicebox"&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/android-auto"&gt;All About Android Auto&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;div class="video"&gt;&lt;div class="video_iframe"&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/ctiaVxgclsg?rel=0&amp;amp;autoplay=0&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&amp;amp;controls=2&amp;amp;autohide=1&amp;amp;showinfo=0" width="680" height="383" class="video-filter video-youtube vf-ctiavxgclsg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!--/video--&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/android-auto-basics"&gt;Getting started with Android Auto&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://forums.androidcentral.com/android-auto/553939-what-has-android-auto-definitive-list-phones-vehicles-aftermarket-units.html"&gt;List of compatible phones and cars&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/android-auto"&gt;Android Auto news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/android-auto-apps"&gt;Apps that work with Android Auto&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="forums.androidcentral.com/android-auto"&gt;Join the Android Auto discussion!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div&gt; &lt;style&gt; &lt;!--/*--&gt;&lt;![CDATA[/* &gt;&lt;!--*/ &lt;!--/*--&gt;&lt;![CDATA[/* &gt;&lt;!--*/ &lt;!--/*--&gt;&lt;![CDATA[/* &gt;&lt;!--*/ /* ALL SIZES */ .devicebox { background: #fff; border: solid #000; border-width: 2px 0; box-sizing: border-box; margin: 0 auto 30px; overflow: auto; padding: 20px 0 15px; position: relative; } div .devicebox ul li, div .devicebox p { box-sizing: border-box; color: #000; display: table; font: 16px "Proxima Nova Th",helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; width: 100%; } .devicebox h3 { color: #000; font: 26px/0.9 "Proxima Nova Bold",helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; margin: 0 0 15px; text-transform: uppercase; } .devicebox a { color: #008099; } .devicebox .video { margin: 0 auto 15px; } .devicebox p { margin: 0px; } .devicebox p.list-head { font: 20px "Proxima Nova Bold",helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; padding: 0 15px; } .devicebox p img, .entry-content .devicebox p &gt; img { width: 100%; } .devicebox ul { display: table; margin: 0 0 10px; width: 100%; } .devicebox ul li { background: #f7f7f7; margin: 2px 0; padding: 4px 15px; } .devicebox ul li:hover { background: #fff; } .devicebox ul li:before { display: none; } .devicebox p ~ p { line-height: 1.25; } .devicebox p:first-of-type + p { padding: 15px; } .devicebox a.buy-link { border-radius: 5px; display: inline-block; font: 14px/31px "Proxima Nova Extrabld",Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; text-align: center; } .devicebox a.buy-link, .devicebox a.buy-link:link, .devicebox a.buy-link:active, .devicebox a.buy-link:visited { background: #37B5D7; color: #FFF; } .devicebox a.buy-link:hover { background: #2694B2; text-decoration: none; } .devicebox a.buy-link:before { content: "\e61e"; font: 40px/0 "ac_iconset" !important; margin: 0 3px 0 -8px; vertical-align: middle; } /* PORTRAIT */ div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) { float: right; margin: 0 0 20px 20px; max-width: 350px; width: 50%; } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox h3, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) h3 { text-align: center; } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) a.buy-link { margin: 0 5px 8px 0; width: calc(50% - 5px); } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(even), div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) .devicebox a.buy-link:last-child, div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(even), div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) .devicebox a.buy-link:last-child { margin-right: 0; } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child { display: block; margin-right: 0; width: auto; } /* LANDSCAPE */ @media all and (min-width: 1025px) { .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox { padding: 20px 0 25px; } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox .video, .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { float: left; margin: 0 30px 0 0; width: calc(100% - 375px); } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { bottom: 20px; display: block; overflow: hidden; position: absolute; top: 59px; } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p img, .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p &gt; img { position: absolute; top: 50%; transform: translateY(-50%); } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p, .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox ul { box-sizing: border-box; margin-left: calc(100% - 345px); width: 340px; } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p.list-head { margin-top: -5px; } } @media all and (min-width: 1025px), all and (max-width: 800px) and (min-width: 660px), all and (max-width: 500px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link { margin: 0 5px 8px 0; width: calc(50% - 5px); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(even), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:last-child { margin-right: 0; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child { display: block; width: auto; } } @media all and (max-width: 800px) and (min-width: 660px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox { padding: 20px 0 25px; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox .video, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { float: left; margin: 0 30px 0 0; width: calc(100% - 375px); } div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { bottom: 20px; display: block; overflow: hidden; position: absolute; top: 59px; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p img, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p &gt; img { position: absolute; top: 50%; transform: translateY(-50%); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox ul { box-sizing: border-box; margin-left: calc(100% - 345px); width: 340px; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p.list-head { margin-top: -5px; } } @media all and (max-width: 1024px) and (min-width: 801px), all and (max-width: 660px) and (min-width: 501px) { div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:before, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) a.buy-link:before { display: none; } } @media all and (max-width: 660px), all and (max-width: 1024px) and (min-width: 801px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 { text-align: center; } div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox ul, div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox p { display: block; } } @media all and (max-width: 660px) and (min-width: 501px), all and (max-width: 1024px) and (min-width: 801px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link { margin: 0 5px 8px 0; width: calc((100% / 3) - 7px); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n):nth-last-child(odd), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n):nth-last-child(n+3) { margin-right: 0; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(2), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(2) ~ a, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(4), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(4) ~ a { width: calc(50% - 5px); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(2) ~ a:nth-last-of-type(odd), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(4) ~ a:nth-last-of-type(odd) { margin-right: 0; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child { display: inline-block; } } @media all and (max-width: 800px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox { margin: 0 0 30px; max-width: none; width: auto; } } @media all and (max-width: 500px) { .devicebox, div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) { float: none; margin: 0 0 30px; max-width: none; width: auto; } .devicebox a.buy-link:before { display: none; } } .page-admin .devicebox {max-width: 350px;} .page-admin .devicebox .video_iframe {position: relative; height: 0; padding-bottom: 56.9%;} .page-admin .devicebox .video_iframe iframe {width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute;} /*--&gt;&lt;!]]]]]]&gt;&lt;![CDATA[&gt;&lt;![CDATA[&gt;*/ /*--&gt;&lt;!]]]]&gt;&lt;![CDATA[&gt;*/ /*--&gt;&lt;!]]&gt;*/ &lt;/style&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386647073/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/fef51qnTojA" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Andrew Martonik</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb7a6a0/sc/23/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Cgoogle0Eplay0Emusic0Eupdate0Eandroid0Eauto0Eremoves0Einteraction0Elimit0Ewhen0Eyour0Ecar0Eparked/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best way to set up your fingerprint on the Galaxy S7</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/zgogl2nW1bU/story01.htm</link>
      <description>It's super easy to set up, but making it work perfectly can take some time. For the most part, setting up and using the fingerprint sensor on the Galaxy S7 is exactly as easy as it's supposed to be. You go through the 13-part process of recording your finger on the sensor, and in exchange you get the ability to unlock your phone quickly and use your fingerprint as your password wherever it is supported. As long as you're down with using your fingerprint like this, it's one of the best setups available today. That is, as long as you set it up correctly. For those who have never set up a fingerprint sensor, or those who have only ever set up a Nexus fingerprint sensor, there are a few things you need to keep in mind when setting up most fingerprint sensors. The set up process is effectively an exercise in taking as many photos of your finger as possible in order to create a complete picture. This way you can put that finger on the sensor in just about any way you want, and as long...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 22:00:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53424 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded>&lt;div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"&gt;&lt;div class="field-items"&gt;&lt;div class="field-item even"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-way-set-your-fingerprint-galaxy-s7' title="The best way to set up your fingerprint on the Galaxy S7"&gt;&lt;img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2016/04/fingerprint-sensor-galaxy-s7.jpg?itok=Oa1cCAfG' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="intro"&gt;It's super easy to set up, but making it work perfectly can take some time.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For the most part, setting up and using the fingerprint sensor on the &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s7"&gt;Galaxy S7&lt;/a&gt; is exactly as easy as it's supposed to be. You go through the 13-part process of recording your finger on the sensor, and in exchange you get the ability to unlock your phone quickly and use your fingerprint as your password wherever it is supported.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As long as you're down with using your fingerprint like this, it's one of the best setups available today. That is, as long as you set it up correctly. &lt;!--break--&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For those who have never set up a fingerprint sensor, or those who have only ever set up &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./nexus-6p"&gt;a Nexus fingerprint sensor&lt;/a&gt;, there are a few things you need to keep in mind when setting up most fingerprint sensors.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The set up process is effectively an exercise in taking as many photos of your finger as possible in order to create a complete picture. This way you can put that finger on the sensor in just about any way you want, and as long as the picture taken when you're unlocking the phone lines up with the complete picture in some way, the phone unlocks. For round sensors like the one on the Nexus phones, it's easy to grab the whole print during setup. Like its predecessors, the Galaxy S7 has an oval sensor, and that means you have to be a little more deliberate during setup.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-way-set-your-fingerprint-galaxy-s7' title="The best way to set up your fingerprint on the Galaxy S7"&gt;&lt;img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2016/04/fingerprint-setup-galaxy-s7.jpg?itok=OcraowhD' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;When setting up a fingerprint on the Galaxy S7, it's important to remember to grab at least two pictures of your thumb going across the sensor diagonally. If all you do is move your thumb from top to bottom or from left to right, it's easy to create gaps in that complete picture. Adding a couple of diagonal captures during setup decreases the chances of this happening, which in turn makes your failure rate significantly lower when unlocking the phone every day.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The oval shape of the Galaxy S7 home button is the real key here. As long as you remember during fingerprint setup that the fingerprint being stored is the result of 13 different presses on the sensor, each capturing a long strip of your thumb and not much else, it becomes a lot easier to deal with. You won't be pressing your finger onto the Galaxy S7's home button the same exact way every time you unlock it, so don't put it on there the same way every time when you're registering it in the first place.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It's also important to remember that you can delete a fingerprint at any time and re-capture that finger if you aren't happy with the results — if you rushed through setup when you first got the phone, it may be worth re-entering your fingers now.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="devicebox"&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s7"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S7 and S7 edge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;div class="video"&gt;&lt;div class="video_iframe"&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/wCpHEsi6NfA?rel=0&amp;amp;autoplay=0&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&amp;amp;controls=2&amp;amp;autohide=1&amp;amp;showinfo=0" width="680" height="383" class="video-filter video-youtube vf-wcphesi6nfa" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!--/video--&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s7-review?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Galaxy S7 review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s7-edge-review?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Galaxy S7 edge review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/samsung-galaxy-s7-edge-review-canadian-perspective?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Galaxy S7 edge with Exynos: A Canadian perspective&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/comparing-galaxy-s7-and-s7-edge-colors?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Here are all four Galaxy S7 colors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/galaxy-s7s-camera-drops-12mp-picks-14-micron-pixels-and-even-faster-focusing?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Details on the Galaxy S7's camera&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/galaxy-s7-regains-microsd-card-shuns-adoptable-storage?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;The SD card is back on the GS7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://forums.androidcentral.com/samsung-galaxy-s7/?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Join our Galaxy S7 forums&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/ext?link=http%3A%2F%2Fclick.linksynergy.com%2Ffs-bin%2Fclick%3Fid%3DJAF5WzpxbKM%26subid%3D%26offerid%3D321145.1%26type%3D10%26tmpid%3D13664%26u1%3Ddac%26RD_PARM1%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fwww.att.com%252Fcellphones%252Fsamsung%252Fgalaxy-s7.html" title="" class="buy-link" rel="nofollow"&gt;AT&amp;amp;T&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sprint.com/apps/new-samsung-galaxy-phone-offers/index.html" title="" class="buy-link"&gt;Sprint&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/ext?link=http%3A%2F%2Ft-mobile.7eer.net%2Fc%2F159229%2F187812%2F3290%3FsubId1%3Dd_ac%26subId2%3Dd_ac%26u%3Dhttp%253A%252F%252Fwww.t-mobile.com%252Fcell-phones%252Fsamsung-galaxy-s7.html" title="" class="buy-link" rel="nofollow"&gt;T-Mobile&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/ext?link=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.jdoqocy.com%2Fclick-7293382-11365093-1445520420000%3Fsid%3Dd_ac%26url%3Dhttp%253A%252F%252Fwww.verizonwireless.com%252Fsmartphones%252Fsamsung-galaxy-s7%252F" title="" class="buy-link" rel="nofollow"&gt;Verizon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div&gt; &lt;style&gt; &lt;!--/*--&gt;&lt;![CDATA[/* &gt;&lt;!--*/ &lt;!--/*--&gt;&lt;![CDATA[/* &gt;&lt;!--*/ &lt;!--/*--&gt;&lt;![CDATA[/* &gt;&lt;!--*/ /* ALL SIZES */ .devicebox { background: #fff; border: solid #000; border-width: 2px 0; box-sizing: border-box; margin: 0 auto 30px; overflow: auto; padding: 20px 0 15px; position: relative; } div .devicebox ul li, div .devicebox p { box-sizing: border-box; color: #000; display: table; font: 16px "Proxima Nova Th",helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; width: 100%; } .devicebox h3 { color: #000; font: 26px/0.9 "Proxima Nova Bold",helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; margin: 0 0 15px; text-transform: uppercase; } .devicebox a { color: #008099; } .devicebox .video { margin: 0 auto 15px; } .devicebox p { margin: 0px; } .devicebox p.list-head { font: 20px "Proxima Nova Bold",helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; padding: 0 15px; } .devicebox p img, .entry-content .devicebox p &gt; img { width: 100%; } .devicebox ul { display: table; margin: 0 0 10px; width: 100%; } .devicebox ul li { background: #f7f7f7; margin: 2px 0; padding: 4px 15px; } .devicebox ul li:hover { background: #fff; } .devicebox ul li:before { display: none; } .devicebox p ~ p { line-height: 1.25; } .devicebox p:first-of-type + p { padding: 15px; } .devicebox a.buy-link { border-radius: 5px; display: inline-block; font: 14px/31px "Proxima Nova Extrabld",Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; text-align: center; } .devicebox a.buy-link, .devicebox a.buy-link:link, .devicebox a.buy-link:active, .devicebox a.buy-link:visited { background: #37B5D7; color: #FFF; } .devicebox a.buy-link:hover { background: #2694B2; text-decoration: none; } .devicebox a.buy-link:before { content: "\e61e"; font: 40px/0 "ac_iconset" !important; margin: 0 3px 0 -8px; vertical-align: middle; } /* PORTRAIT */ div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) { float: right; margin: 0 0 20px 20px; max-width: 350px; width: 50%; } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox h3, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) h3 { text-align: center; } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) a.buy-link { margin: 0 5px 8px 0; width: calc(50% - 5px); } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(even), div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) .devicebox a.buy-link:last-child, div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(even), div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) .devicebox a.buy-link:last-child { margin-right: 0; } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child { display: block; margin-right: 0; width: auto; } /* LANDSCAPE */ @media all and (min-width: 1025px) { .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox { padding: 20px 0 25px; } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox .video, .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { float: left; margin: 0 30px 0 0; width: calc(100% - 375px); } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { bottom: 20px; display: block; overflow: hidden; position: absolute; top: 59px; } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p img, .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p &gt; img { position: absolute; top: 50%; transform: translateY(-50%); } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p, .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox ul { box-sizing: border-box; margin-left: calc(100% - 345px); width: 340px; } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p.list-head { margin-top: -5px; } } @media all and (min-width: 1025px), all and (max-width: 800px) and (min-width: 660px), all and (max-width: 500px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link { margin: 0 5px 8px 0; width: calc(50% - 5px); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(even), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:last-child { margin-right: 0; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child { display: block; width: auto; } } @media all and (max-width: 800px) and (min-width: 660px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox { padding: 20px 0 25px; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox .video, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { float: left; margin: 0 30px 0 0; width: calc(100% - 375px); } div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { bottom: 20px; display: block; overflow: hidden; position: absolute; top: 59px; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p img, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p &gt; img { position: absolute; top: 50%; transform: translateY(-50%); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox ul { box-sizing: border-box; margin-left: calc(100% - 345px); width: 340px; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p.list-head { margin-top: -5px; } } @media all and (max-width: 1024px) and (min-width: 801px), all and (max-width: 660px) and (min-width: 501px) { div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:before, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) a.buy-link:before { display: none; } } @media all and (max-width: 660px), all and (max-width: 1024px) and (min-width: 801px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 { text-align: center; } div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox ul, div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox p { display: block; } } @media all and (max-width: 660px) and (min-width: 501px), all and (max-width: 1024px) and (min-width: 801px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link { margin: 0 5px 8px 0; width: calc((100% / 3) - 7px); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n):nth-last-child(odd), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n):nth-last-child(n+3) { margin-right: 0; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(2), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(2) ~ a, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(4), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(4) ~ a { width: calc(50% - 5px); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(2) ~ a:nth-last-of-type(odd), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(4) ~ a:nth-last-of-type(odd) { margin-right: 0; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child { display: inline-block; } } @media all and (max-width: 800px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox { margin: 0 0 30px; max-width: none; width: auto; } } @media all and (max-width: 500px) { .devicebox, div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) { float: none; margin: 0 0 30px; max-width: none; width: auto; } .devicebox a.buy-link:before { display: none; } } .page-admin .devicebox {max-width: 350px;} .page-admin .devicebox .video_iframe {position: relative; height: 0; padding-bottom: 56.9%;} .page-admin .devicebox .video_iframe iframe {width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute;} /*--&gt;&lt;!]]]]]]&gt;&lt;![CDATA[&gt;&lt;![CDATA[&gt;*/ /*--&gt;&lt;!]]]]&gt;&lt;![CDATA[&gt;*/ /*--&gt;&lt;!]]&gt;*/ &lt;/style&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386646371/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/zgogl2nW1bU" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Russell Holly</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb7a3bf/sc/15/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Cbest0Eway0Eset0Eyour0Efingerprint0Egalaxy0Es7/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTC 10 teaser promises the 'best BoomSound yet'</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/TgLI1yf_xVc/story01.htm</link>
      <description>HTC hasn't been shy about teasing what's in store for the upcoming HTC 10, and the company's latest teaser continues that tradition by hinting at the phone's booming audio chops. In a quick, flashy video posted to Twitter, HTC says its obsession with high-quality sound means that the HTC 10 will pack "the best BoomSound yet." Not all music is created equal. Hi-res audio so every note is crystal clear. You'll hear it. 4/12 #powerof10https://t.co/uSFPDg4t6o— HTC (@htc) April 4, 2016 HTC has already teased the camera, capacitive buttons and more that will appear on the HTC 10, and it won't be long before we get to see the much-anticipated handset unveiled in the flesh at HTC's April 12 launch. Are you excited to get your hands on the HTC 10? Let us know what you're looking forward to most in the comments! ...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 21:42:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53442 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"><div class="field-items"><div class="field-item even"><p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/htc-10-teaser-promises-best-boomsound-yet' title="HTC 10 teaser promises the 'best BoomSound yet'"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2015/07/htc-logo-balls-angle-mwc2015-hero.jpg?itok=fqILxOih' /></a></p> <p>HTC hasn't been shy about teasing what's in store for the upcoming <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/htc-10">HTC 10</a>, and the company's latest teaser continues that tradition by hinting at the phone's booming audio chops. <!--break--> In a quick, flashy video <a href="https://twitter.com/htc/status/717019520913682433?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">posted to Twitter</a>, HTC says its obsession with high-quality sound means that the HTC 10 will pack "the best BoomSound yet."</p> <blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"><p lang="en" dir="ltr" xml:lang="en">Not all music is created equal. Hi-res audio so every note is crystal clear. You'll hear it. 4/12 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/powerof10?src=hash">#powerof10</a><a href="https://t.co/uSFPDg4t6o">https://t.co/uSFPDg4t6o</a></p>— HTC (@htc) <a href="https://twitter.com/htc/status/717019520913682433">April 4, 2016</a></blockquote> <script async="" src="//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><p>HTC has already teased the camera, capacitive buttons and more that will appear on the HTC 10, and it won't be long before we get to see the much-anticipated handset unveiled in the flesh at HTC's April 12 launch.</p> <p>Are you excited to get your hands on the HTC 10? Let us know what you're looking forward to most in the comments!</p> </div></div></div><br clear='all'/><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/a2.htm"><img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/a2.img" border="0"/></a><img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386646253/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/a2t.img" border="0"/><img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/mf.gif' border='0'/><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/TgLI1yf_xVc" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Dan Thorp-Lancaster</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb7a341/sc/15/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Chtc0E10A0Eteaser0Epromises0Ebest0Eboomsound0Eyet/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTC Vive is the VR system that has won your hearts</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/BX6gl8fsORU/story01.htm</link>
      <description>In last week's poll we asked which VR system you are the most excited about. There are options out there whether you're interested in VR on your computer, your video game console, or even your phone. With this much variety involved, we wanted to know where your interest in pointed. Of all the VR systems out there, the HTC Vive seems to be the one that caught your eye. The HTC Vive slid into first place with a solid 24 percent of the vote. Just behind it, in second place with 21 percent of the vote, was "I'm not that interested in VR right now". The Gear VR took a solid third place with 18 percent of the vote. Playstation VR managed to snag a solid 16 percent of the vote, letting it coast easily into third place. The Oculus Rift snagged 13 percent of the vote to take fifth place in our poll, and "I haven't decided yet" picked up 9 percent of the vote landing it in last place. While the HTC Vive took 24 percent of the poll landing in first place, it's also worth pointing out that 30...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 21:00:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53429 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"><div class="field-items"><div class="field-item even"><p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/htc-vive-vr-system-has-won-your-hearts' title="HTC Vive is the VR system that has won your hearts "><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2016/02/htc-vive-consumer-22.jpg?itok=sfAOjuyG' /></a></p> <p>In last week's poll we asked <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/.//which-vr-system-has-you-most-excited">which VR system you are the most excited about</a>. There are options out there whether you're interested in VR on your computer, your video game console, or even your phone. With this much variety involved, we wanted to know where your interest in pointed. Of all the VR systems out there, the <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./htc-vive">HTC Vive</a> seems to be the one that caught your eye.</p> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/htc-vive-vr-system-has-won-your-hearts' title="HTC Vive is the VR system that has won your hearts "><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2016/04/poll-followup-htc-vive-wins-at-vr.jpeg?itok=KTcQxnAX' /></a></p> <p>The HTC Vive slid into first place with a solid 24 percent of the vote. Just behind it, in second place with 21 percent of the vote, was "I'm not that interested in VR right now". The <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-gear-vr">Gear VR</a> took a solid third place with 18 percent of the vote. <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/playstation-vr/home">Playstation VR</a> managed to snag a solid 16 percent of the vote, letting it coast easily into third place. The <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./oculus-rift">Oculus Rift</a> snagged 13 percent of the vote to take fifth place in our poll, and "I haven't decided yet" picked up 9 percent of the vote landing it in last place. While the HTC Vive took 24 percent of the poll landing in first place, it's also worth pointing out that 30 percent of you are either uninterested in VR, or still trying to decide on the best system for you.</p> <p>Did your favorite system win out in our poll? Are you vibrating with excitement about the HTC Vive? Let us know all about it in the comments!</p> </div></div></div><br clear='all'/><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/a2.htm"><img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/a2.img" border="0"/></a><img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386674886/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/a2t.img" border="0"/><img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/mf.gif' border='0'/><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/BX6gl8fsORU" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Jen Karner</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb7560f/sc/21/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Chtc0Evive0Evr0Esystem0Ehas0Ewon0Eyour0Ehearts/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Auto expands to 18 new countries, plus Puerto Rico</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/J6F6uOJqrYY/story01.htm</link>
      <description>More people around the world will be able to start experiencing Android Auto, as the feature is now available in many more countries across the globe. In all, Android Auto has expanded to a total of 18 new countries (and one territory, for good measure) across Latin America, Europe and elsewhere, including: Argentina Austria Bolivia Brazil Chile Colombia Costa Rica Dominican Republic Ecuador Guatemala India Panama Paraguay Peru Puerto Rico Russia Switzerland Uruguay Venezuela If you call one of the above home and your car is sporting Android Auto, you should be able to start taking advantage of the feature right away. ...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 19:48:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53439 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"><div class="field-items"><div class="field-item even"><p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/android-auto-expands-18-new-countries' title="Android Auto expands to 18 new countries, plus Puerto Rico"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2015/10/nexus-5x-android-auto.jpg?itok=KoeovhvC' /></a></p> <p>More people around the world will be able to start experiencing <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/android-auto">Android Auto</a>, as the feature is now available in many more countries across the globe. <!--break--> In all, Android Auto has <a href="https://twitter.com/Android/status/717064192361148416">expanded to a total of 18 new countries</a> (and one territory, for good measure) across Latin America, Europe and elsewhere, including:</p> <ul class="col2"><li>Argentina</li> <li>Austria</li> <li>Bolivia</li> <li>Brazil</li> <li>Chile</li> <li>Colombia</li> <li>Costa Rica</li> <li>Dominican Republic</li> <li>Ecuador</li> <li>Guatemala</li> <li>India</li> <li>Panama</li> <li>Paraguay</li> <li>Peru</li> <li>Puerto Rico</li> <li>Russia</li> <li>Switzerland</li> <li>Uruguay</li> <li>Venezuela</li> </ul><p>If you call one of the above home and your car is sporting Android Auto, you should be able to start taking advantage of the feature right away.</p> </div></div></div><br clear='all'/><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/a2.htm"><img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/a2.img" border="0"/></a><img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386645444/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/a2t.img" border="0"/><img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/mf.gif' border='0'/><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/J6F6uOJqrYY" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Dan Thorp-Lancaster</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb5b6de/sc/28/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Candroid0Eauto0Eexpands0E180Enew0Ecountries/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best in-ear headphones</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/Z3LBejCQMx8/story01.htm</link>
      <description>Our editors share their picks for the best in-ear headphones available today! Choosing a pair of in-ear headphones is tough. We all have different tastes, budgets, and needs. So we rounded up a group of people used to making tough choices — our Mobile Nations editors. They've shared the in-ear headphones they're using and, more importantly, why! Phil Nickinson - Bose QuietComfort 20 Acoustic Noise Cancelling Headphones If you spend any amount of time on airplanes, you need noise-canceling headphones. And the QC20 from Bose will change your life. It's active noise-cancellation, which means there's a small, thin box toward the bottom of the cable that houses the battery and electronics. It's a little clunky, but that's the price of admission. It also has to be charged periodically — I've only ever done it before a big trip, and maybe before heading home, if it's going to be a particularly long flight. But it charges over microUSB, so that's easy enough. The result is nig...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb55554/sc/28/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 18:45:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53436 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"><div class="field-items"><div class="field-item even"><p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-ear-headphones' title="The Best in-ear headphones"><img src='http://www.imore.com/sites/imore.com/files/styles/large/public/field/image/2016/04/earphones-ugly-beard-guy.jpg?itok=H3GLqeoC' /></a></p> <p class="intro">Our editors share their picks for the best in-ear headphones available today!</p> <p>Choosing a pair of in-ear headphones is tough. We all have different tastes, budgets, and needs. So we rounded up a group of people used to making tough choices — our Mobile Nations editors. They've shared the in-ear headphones they're using and, more importantly, why!</p> <!--break--> <h2>Phil Nickinson - Bose QuietComfort 20 Acoustic Noise Cancelling Headphones</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-ear-headphones' title="The Best in-ear headphones"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/field/image/2016/04/phil-gearbag-2016-5.jpg?itok=PxUPNnnT' /></a></p> <p>If you spend any amount of time on airplanes, you need noise-canceling headphones. And the <a href="http://www.amazon.com/Bose-QuietComfort-Acoustic-Cancelling-Headphones/dp/B00X9KV0HU/ref=sr_1_1?s=electronics&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1459509337&amp;sr=1-1&amp;keywords=bose+qc20&amp;tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" rel="nofollow">QC20 from Bose</a> will change your life. It's active noise-cancellation, which means there's a small, thin box toward the bottom of the cable that houses the battery and electronics. It's a little clunky, but that's the price of admission.</p> <p>It also has to be charged periodically — I've only ever done it before a big trip, and maybe before heading home, if it's going to be a particularly long flight. But it charges over microUSB, so that's easy enough.</p> <p>The result is night and day. Music no longer has to be turned up dangerously loud. Voices are easy to understand. Engine noise all but disappears. It's actually almost disorienting at first. But you'll soon find you can't live without it. And I haven' even mentioned the sound quality. (It's Bose. It's good.) Priced at around $299, these aren't cheap headphones, but they're excellent. I don't fly anywhere without them.</p> <p><a href="http://www.amazon.com/Bose-QuietComfort-Acoustic-Cancelling-Headphones/dp/B00X9KV0HU/ref=sr_1_1?s=electronics&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1459509337&amp;sr=1-1&amp;keywords=bose+qc20&amp;tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" class="cta shop" rel="nofollow">See at Amazon</a></p> <h2>Daniel Bader - RHA T10i</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-ear-headphones' title="The Best in-ear headphones"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/field/image/2016/04/rha-t10i-headphones.jpg?itok=KUBO5O4R' /></a></p> <p>RHA is a relatively unknown company, but it makes high-quality in-ear headphones with extremely good sound quality and enviable designs.</p> <p>The <a href="http://www.amazon.com/RHA-T10i-Isolating-Headphone-Microphone/dp/B00OY2T9U2/ref=sr_1_2?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1459508971&amp;sr=8-2&amp;keywords=rha+t10&amp;tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" rel="nofollow">T10i</a> was, until early 2016, the company's flagship in-ear monitors, featuring flat (but customizable) sound characteristics (via replaceable filters, emphasizing treble, bass, etc.), and easy-to-mould over-ear hooks for comfortable wear.</p> <p>Though expensive at just under $200, the T10i's come with multiple ear tips in both silicone and memory foam, and have a long warranty in case anything happens to them.</p> <p><a href="http://www.amazon.com/RHA-T10i-Isolating-Headphone-Microphone/dp/B00OY2T9U2/ref=sr_1_2?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1459508971&amp;sr=8-2&amp;keywords=rha+t10&amp;tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" class="cta shop" rel="nofollow">See at Amazon</a></p> <h2>Daniel Rubino - Bose SoundSport In-Ear Headphones</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-ear-headphones' title="The Best in-ear headphones"><img src='http://www.imore.com/sites/imore.com/files/styles/large/public/field/image/2016/04/bose-green-fixed.jpg?itok=lbLHoufO' /></a></p> <p>I use them for exercising as I do not have to recharge them (problem with wireless). They look good, are super comfortable, and have excellent sound quality. I have the Microsoft 'green' ones as they stand out and I can easily find them in my gym bag.</p> <p><a href="http://www.amazon.com/Bose-SoundSport-in-ear-headphones-Charcoal/dp/B011IH5ZHG/ref=sr_1_1?s=electronics&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1459509374&amp;sr=1-1-spons&amp;keywords=bose+soundsport&amp;psc=1&amp;tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" class="cta shop" rel="nofollow">See at Amazon</a></p> <h2>Richard Devine - RHA T10</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-ear-headphones' title="The Best in-ear headphones"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/field/image/2016/04/rha-t10-1.jpg?itok=k2ntKmGG' /></a></p> <p>The slightly less expensive companion to the T10i, the main difference to the <a href="http://www.amazon.com/RHA-T10-Fidelity-Isolating-Headphone/dp/B00P0N19LQ/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1459508971&amp;sr=8-1&amp;keywords=rha+t10&amp;tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" rel="nofollow">T10</a> is the lack of an in-line remote. Otherwise they're the exact same earbuds with great sound and the ability to swap out the filters in the middle to add more bass or more treble as you so desire. The sheer multitude of different sized tips included in the pack as well means you're sure of getting a good fit, even with odd ears like mine.</p> <p>The T10s are so comfortable it's ridiculous. I wore these almost completely straight through a 13 hour flight with no discomfort whatsoever. There is an element of passive noise cancellation, so noisy plane engines aren't totally going to drive you mad, but active cancelling is about all I wish these phenomenally good earbuds had.</p> <p>They're not cheap, but they're absolutely worth the money. A blend of sheer comfort and great sound quality means they'd be tough to replace for me.</p> <p><a href="http://www.amazon.com/RHA-T10-Fidelity-Isolating-Headphone/dp/B00P0N19LQ/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1459508971&amp;sr=8-1&amp;keywords=rha+t10&amp;tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" class="cta shop" rel="nofollow">See at Amazon</a></p> <h2>Mike Tanasychuk - Apple Earpods</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-ear-headphones' title="The Best in-ear headphones"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/field/image/2014/05/apple_earpods_hero.jpg?itok=qKOPAJe5' /></a></p> <p>For in-ear headphones that just come with a device (iPod or iPhone), they have to be some of the best-sounding headphones I've ever used.</p> <p>The bass tones are very rich and warm and the mid and highs are balanced really well. All levels sing out nicely and it's really easy to hear harmonies and to separate tracks. Whenever I'm trying to learn a drum or guitar part, these headphones more than do the trick. They may not be much for noise cancelling, but I've never had any decline in audio quality because I've cranked 'em.</p> <p>They also seem to last the longest out of any in-ear headphones I've used. The plastic doesn't feel cheap; the rubber cord is formidable and won't tear (at least, it hasn't for me); I can usually get a couple years out of a pair.</p> <p><a href="http://www.amazon.com/Apple-MD827LL-A-EarPods-Remote/dp/B0097BEG1C/ref=sr_1_2?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1459509177&amp;sr=8-2&amp;keywords=apple+earpods&amp;tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" class="cta shop" rel="nofollow">See at Amazon</a></p> <h2>DJ Reyes - BlackBerry Premium Headset WS-410</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-ear-headphones' title="The Best in-ear headphones"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/field/image/2016/04/blackberry-premium-headphones.jpg?itok=MTzCFMhu' /></a></p> <p>I prefer in-ear headphones rather than over-the-ear ones for travelling because they're easier to carry around and slip into a pocket. I've tried many over the years but there's one that beats all others - the <a href="http://www.amazon.com/WS-430-Premium-Multimedia-Stereo-Headset/dp/B00ELAHZ44/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1459509248&amp;sr=8-1&amp;keywords=blackberry+premium+headset&amp;tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" rel="nofollow">BlackBerry Premium Headset</a>.</p> <p>They're the ones that come in the BlackBerry 10 device boxes. I use them not so much for the sound quality, which is good enough for me still. Not for the noise cancelling function because it doesn't have that feature but because they fit and don't fall out of my ear. They fit securely in my ear, in-part thanks to wing-hoop on the ear piece that helps to secure it in place. On top of that, these headphones are not the kind that have to go into my ear canal. Even with those wing tips that come with other in-ear headphones, they never fit in my ear, no matter what size piece I use. Perhaps I'm wearing them wrong but I've never really got on well with the ones that have to go into the ear canal, those always pop out.</p> <p>The in-line microphone and one-touch button comes in handy when I need to take a phone call and the flat wire design means I don't have to spend time untangling them when I want to use them. I may upgrade to the slightly better model which includes volume keys but for now this WS-410 model suits me just fine.</p> <p><a href="http://www.amazon.com/WS-430-Premium-Multimedia-Stereo-Headset/dp/B00ELAHZ44/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1459509248&amp;sr=8-1&amp;keywords=blackberry+premium+headset&amp;tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" class="cta shop" rel="nofollow">See at Amazon</a></p> <h2>Michael Fisher - HTC Active Earbuds</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-ear-headphones' title="The Best in-ear headphones"><img src='http://www.imore.com/sites/imore.com/files/styles/large/public/field/image/2016/04/htc-rc-e250-headset-yellow-2-gallery.png?itok=e0-iNhkM' /></a></p> <p>A design that's dust- and water-resistant (and therefore pocket- and sweat-resistant). Textured metal housings and eye-catching yellow trim. A three-button control collective for music and phone calls. And the buds magically come together when brought back to back thanks to the power of magnets.</p> <p>It's tough to make earbuds stand out in 2016, but HTC does it with the <a href="http://www.amazon.com/HTC-Active-Headset-One-Packaging/dp/B00UN3YPC8?tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" rel="nofollow">Active Headset</a>. Toss in respectable sound quality, a comfy in-ear feel and a reasonable price point, and you'd be hard-pressed to find a better set of buds for your rainy-day hiking trips.</p> <p><a href="http://www.amazon.com/HTC-Active-Headset-One-Packaging/dp/B00UN3YPC8?tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" class="cta shop" rel="nofollow">See at Amazon</a></p> </div></div></div><br clear='all'/><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/a2.htm"><img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/a2.img" border="0"/></a><img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386673665/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55554/sc/28/a2t.img" border="0"/><img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb55554/sc/28/mf.gif' border='0'/><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/Z3LBejCQMx8" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Richard Devine</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb55554/sc/28/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Cbest0Eear0Eheadphones/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>April security patch now available for the BlackBerry Priv</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/h11HotDM7fs/story01.htm</link>
      <description>The April security patches are now available for BlackBerry Priv owners. Those who purchased their phones from ShopBlackBerry may have already received the update on March 23, but now more carriers are pushing it. This update patches the latest round of vulnerabilities that Google discovered, keeping your phone even more secure. BlackBerry has posted additional details about the update as well if you wish to check those out. To check your phone for an update, head into the Settings, About phone and check for update. Be sure to let us know in the comments once you've received it. ...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb55555/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 18:31:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53437 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"><div class="field-items"><div class="field-item even"><p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/april-security-patch-now-available-blackberry-priv' title="April security patch now available for the BlackBerry Priv"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_blw/public/article_images/2016/03/priv-update-march.jpg?itok=_MiWJ2Ms' /></a></p> <p>The April security patches are now available for <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./blackberry-priv">BlackBerry Priv</a> owners. Those who purchased their phones from ShopBlackBerry may have already received the update on March 23, but now more carriers are pushing it. This update <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/android-april-2-security-patch-live-here-are-details-you-need-know">patches the latest round of vulnerabilities</a> that Google discovered, keeping your phone even more secure. <!--break--></p> <p><a href="http://support.blackberry.com/kb/articleDetail?articleNumber=000038099&amp;language=English">BlackBerry has posted additional details</a> about the update as well if you wish to check those out. To check your phone for an update, head into the Settings, About phone and check for update. Be sure to let us know in the comments once you've received it.</p> </div></div></div><br clear='all'/><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/a2.htm"><img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/></a><img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386673664/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb55555/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/><img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb55555/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/h11HotDM7fs" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Jared DiPane</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb55555/sc/23/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Capril0Esecurity0Epatch0Enow0Eavailable0Eblackberry0Epriv/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We're giving away a Samsung Galaxy S7 or S7 edge! [International contest!!!]</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/suQUMZiEfOs/story01.htm</link>
      <description>Winner's choice! It's time to give away another phone, and this time the winner gets to choose between the Galaxy S7 or S7 edge. Everything you need to know to enter is below, so scroll on down and check it out. How to Enter: Head down to the widget at the bottom of this page. There are multiple ways to enter, each with varying point values. For example, you can participate in the forums for 10 entries, comment on this blog post for an entry, and follow us on various social media channels for even more entries. Complete all of the tasks for maximum entries and your best shot at winning! The giveaway is open until April 6th, and winners will be announced on the blog shortly after the close date. The Prize: One super lucky Android Central reader will take home a brand new Samsung Galaxy S7 or S7 edge! Please note that service is not included with the phone. Also, in the event that the winner resides outside of the United States, the prize maybe be subject to duties and taxes, whic...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 18:21:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52887 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded>&lt;div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"&gt;&lt;div class="field-items"&gt;&lt;div class="field-item even"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/were-giving-away-another-samsung-galaxy-s7-or-s7-edge' title="We're giving away a Samsung Galaxy S7 or S7 edge! [International contest!!!]"&gt;&lt;img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2016/03/galaxy-s7-edge-gold-white-black-backs_0.jpg?itok=-XKmUMH3' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="intro"&gt;Winner's choice!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It's time to give away another phone, and this time the winner gets to choose between the &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s7"&gt;Galaxy S7&lt;/a&gt; or S7 edge. Everything you need to know to enter is below, so scroll on down and check it out.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Enter&lt;/strong&gt;: Head down to the widget at the bottom of this page. There are multiple ways to enter, each with varying point values. For example, you can participate in the forums for 10 entries, comment on this blog post for an entry, and follow us on various social media channels for even more entries. Complete all of the tasks for maximum entries and your best shot at winning!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The giveaway is open until April 6th, and winners will be announced on the blog shortly after the close date.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Prize&lt;/strong&gt;: One super lucky Android Central reader will take home a brand new Samsung Galaxy S7 or S7 edge!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please note that service is not included with the phone. Also, in the event that the winner resides outside of the United States, the prize maybe be subject to duties and taxes, which are the responsibility of the winner.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Good luck everybody!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="e-widget generic-loader" href="https://gleam.io/yssYK/win-the-new-samsung-galaxy-s7-or-s7-edge-from-android-central-" rel="nofollow"&gt;Win the new Samsung Galaxy S7 or S7 edge from Android Central! &lt;/a&gt; &lt;script type="text/javascript" src="https://js.gleam.io/e.js" async="true"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="devicebox"&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s7"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S7 and S7 edge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;div class="video"&gt;&lt;div class="video_iframe"&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/wCpHEsi6NfA?rel=0&amp;amp;autoplay=0&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&amp;amp;controls=2&amp;amp;autohide=1&amp;amp;showinfo=0" width="680" height="383" class="video-filter video-youtube vf-wcphesi6nfa" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!--/video--&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s7-review?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Galaxy S7 review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s7-edge-review?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Galaxy S7 edge review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/samsung-galaxy-s7-edge-review-canadian-perspective?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Galaxy S7 edge with Exynos: A Canadian perspective&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/comparing-galaxy-s7-and-s7-edge-colors?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Here are all four Galaxy S7 colors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/galaxy-s7s-camera-drops-12mp-picks-14-micron-pixels-and-even-faster-focusing?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Details on the Galaxy S7's camera&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/galaxy-s7-regains-microsd-card-shuns-adoptable-storage?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;The SD card is back on the GS7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://forums.androidcentral.com/samsung-galaxy-s7/?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Join our Galaxy S7 forums&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/ext?link=http%3A%2F%2Fclick.linksynergy.com%2Ffs-bin%2Fclick%3Fid%3DJAF5WzpxbKM%26subid%3D%26offerid%3D321145.1%26type%3D10%26tmpid%3D13664%26u1%3Ddac%26RD_PARM1%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fwww.att.com%252Fcellphones%252Fsamsung%252Fgalaxy-s7.html" title="" class="buy-link" rel="nofollow"&gt;AT&amp;amp;T&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sprint.com/apps/new-samsung-galaxy-phone-offers/index.html" title="" class="buy-link"&gt;Sprint&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/ext?link=http%3A%2F%2Ft-mobile.7eer.net%2Fc%2F159229%2F187812%2F3290%3FsubId1%3Dd_ac%26subId2%3Dd_ac%26u%3Dhttp%253A%252F%252Fwww.t-mobile.com%252Fcell-phones%252Fsamsung-galaxy-s7.html" title="" class="buy-link" rel="nofollow"&gt;T-Mobile&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/ext?link=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.jdoqocy.com%2Fclick-7293382-11365093-1445520420000%3Fsid%3Dd_ac%26url%3Dhttp%253A%252F%252Fwww.verizonwireless.com%252Fsmartphones%252Fsamsung-galaxy-s7%252F" title="" class="buy-link" rel="nofollow"&gt;Verizon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div&gt; &lt;style&gt; &lt;!--/*--&gt;&lt;![CDATA[/* &gt;&lt;!--*/ &lt;!--/*--&gt;&lt;![CDATA[/* &gt;&lt;!--*/ &lt;!--/*--&gt;&lt;![CDATA[/* &gt;&lt;!--*/ /* ALL SIZES */ .devicebox { background: #fff; border: solid #000; border-width: 2px 0; box-sizing: border-box; margin: 0 auto 30px; overflow: auto; padding: 20px 0 15px; position: relative; } div .devicebox ul li, div .devicebox p { box-sizing: border-box; color: #000; display: table; font: 16px "Proxima Nova Th",helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; width: 100%; } .devicebox h3 { color: #000; font: 26px/0.9 "Proxima Nova Bold",helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; margin: 0 0 15px; text-transform: uppercase; } .devicebox a { color: #008099; } .devicebox .video { margin: 0 auto 15px; } .devicebox p { margin: 0px; } .devicebox p.list-head { font: 20px "Proxima Nova Bold",helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; padding: 0 15px; } .devicebox p img, .entry-content .devicebox p &gt; img { width: 100%; } .devicebox ul { display: table; margin: 0 0 10px; width: 100%; } .devicebox ul li { background: #f7f7f7; margin: 2px 0; padding: 4px 15px; } .devicebox ul li:hover { background: #fff; } .devicebox ul li:before { display: none; } .devicebox p ~ p { line-height: 1.25; } .devicebox p:first-of-type + p { padding: 15px; } .devicebox a.buy-link { border-radius: 5px; display: inline-block; font: 14px/31px "Proxima Nova Extrabld",Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; text-align: center; } .devicebox a.buy-link, .devicebox a.buy-link:link, .devicebox a.buy-link:active, .devicebox a.buy-link:visited { background: #37B5D7; color: #FFF; } .devicebox a.buy-link:hover { background: #2694B2; text-decoration: none; } .devicebox a.buy-link:before { content: "\e61e"; font: 40px/0 "ac_iconset" !important; margin: 0 3px 0 -8px; vertical-align: middle; } /* PORTRAIT */ div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) { float: right; margin: 0 0 20px 20px; max-width: 350px; width: 50%; } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox h3, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) h3 { text-align: center; } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) a.buy-link { margin: 0 5px 8px 0; width: calc(50% - 5px); } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(even), div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) .devicebox a.buy-link:last-child, div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(even), div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) .devicebox a.buy-link:last-child { margin-right: 0; } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child { display: block; margin-right: 0; width: auto; } /* LANDSCAPE */ @media all and (min-width: 1025px) { .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox { padding: 20px 0 25px; } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox .video, .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { float: left; margin: 0 30px 0 0; width: calc(100% - 375px); } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { bottom: 20px; display: block; overflow: hidden; position: absolute; top: 59px; } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p img, .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p &gt; img { position: absolute; top: 50%; transform: translateY(-50%); } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p, .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox ul { box-sizing: border-box; margin-left: calc(100% - 345px); width: 340px; } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p.list-head { margin-top: -5px; } } @media all and (min-width: 1025px), all and (max-width: 800px) and (min-width: 660px), all and (max-width: 500px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link { margin: 0 5px 8px 0; width: calc(50% - 5px); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(even), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:last-child { margin-right: 0; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child { display: block; width: auto; } } @media all and (max-width: 800px) and (min-width: 660px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox { padding: 20px 0 25px; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox .video, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { float: left; margin: 0 30px 0 0; width: calc(100% - 375px); } div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { bottom: 20px; display: block; overflow: hidden; position: absolute; top: 59px; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p img, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p &gt; img { position: absolute; top: 50%; transform: translateY(-50%); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox ul { box-sizing: border-box; margin-left: calc(100% - 345px); width: 340px; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p.list-head { margin-top: -5px; } } @media all and (max-width: 1024px) and (min-width: 801px), all and (max-width: 660px) and (min-width: 501px) { div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:before, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) a.buy-link:before { display: none; } } @media all and (max-width: 660px), all and (max-width: 1024px) and (min-width: 801px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 { text-align: center; } div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox ul, div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox p { display: block; } } @media all and (max-width: 660px) and (min-width: 501px), all and (max-width: 1024px) and (min-width: 801px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link { margin: 0 5px 8px 0; width: calc((100% / 3) - 7px); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n):nth-last-child(odd), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n):nth-last-child(n+3) { margin-right: 0; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(2), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(2) ~ a, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(4), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(4) ~ a { width: calc(50% - 5px); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(2) ~ a:nth-last-of-type(odd), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(4) ~ a:nth-last-of-type(odd) { margin-right: 0; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child { display: inline-block; } } @media all and (max-width: 800px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox { margin: 0 0 30px; max-width: none; width: auto; } } @media all and (max-width: 500px) { .devicebox, div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) { float: none; margin: 0 0 30px; max-width: none; width: auto; } .devicebox a.buy-link:before { display: none; } } .page-admin .devicebox {max-width: 350px;} .page-admin .devicebox .video_iframe {position: relative; height: 0; padding-bottom: 56.9%;} .page-admin .devicebox .video_iframe iframe {width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute;} /*--&gt;&lt;!]]]]]]&gt;&lt;![CDATA[&gt;&lt;![CDATA[&gt;*/ /*--&gt;&lt;!]]]]&gt;&lt;![CDATA[&gt;*/ /*--&gt;&lt;!]]&gt;*/ &lt;/style&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386673558/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/suQUMZiEfOs" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Michelle Haag</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb554c1/sc/23/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Cwere0Egiving0Eaway0Eanother0Esamsung0Egalaxy0Es70Eor0Es70Eedge/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Android April 2 security patch is live - here are the details you need to know</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/5q4DSLnJX_Q/story01.htm</link>
      <description>The Android security patch dated April 2, 2016 is up and running — factory images are available and code is being updated. Google has released the details surrounding the April 2 security patch for Android, completely mitigating issues described in a bulletin several weeks ago as well as a slew or other critical and moderate issues. This one is a bit different from previous bulletins, with special attention paid to a privilege escalation vulnerability in versions 3.4, 3.10 and 3.14 of the Linux kernel used in Android. We'll discuss that further down the page. In the meantime, here's the breakdown of what you need to know about this month's patch. Updated firmware images are now available for currently supported Nexus devices on the Google Developer site. The Android Open Source Project has these changes rolling out to the relevant branches now, and everything will be complete and synchronized within 48 hours. Over the air updates are in progress for currently supported Nexus ph...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 17:44:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53419 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"><div class="field-items"><div class="field-item even"><p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/android-april-2-security-patch-live-here-are-details-you-need-know' title="The Android April 2 security patch is live - here are the details you need to know"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2016/02/nexus-5x-black-back-angle.jpg?itok=n8W3U5nd' /></a></p> <p class="intro">The Android security patch dated April 2, 2016 is up and running — factory images are available and code is being updated.</p> <p>Google has <a href="http://source.android.com/security/bulletin/">released the details</a> surrounding the April 2 security patch for Android, completely mitigating issues described in a bulletin several weeks ago as well as a slew or other critical and moderate issues. This one is a bit different from previous bulletins, with special attention paid to a privilege escalation vulnerability in versions 3.4, 3.10 and 3.14 of the Linux kernel used in Android. We'll discuss that further down the page. In the meantime, here's the breakdown of what you need to know about this month's patch.</p> <!--break--> <p>Updated firmware images are now available for currently supported Nexus devices on the <a href="https://developers.google.com/android/nexus/images">Google Developer site</a>. The Android Open Source Project has these changes rolling out to the relevant branches now, and everything will be complete and synchronized within 48 hours. Over the air updates are in progress for currently supported Nexus phones and tablets, and will follow the standard Google rollout procedure — it may take a week or two to get to your Nexus. All partners — that means the people who built your phone, regardless of brand — have had access to these fixes as of March 16 2016, and they will announce and patch devices on their own individual schedules.</p> <p>The most severe issue addressed is a vulnerability that could allow remote code execution when processing media files. These files can be sent to your phone by any means — email, web browsing MMS or instant messaging. Other critical issues patched are specific to the DHCP client, Qualcomm's Performance Module and RF driver. These exploits could allow code to run that permanently compromises the device firmware, forcing the end user to need to re-flash the full operating system — if "platform and service mitigations are disabled for development proposes." That's security-nerd speak for allowing apps from unknown sources to be installed and/or allowing OEM unlocking.</p> <p>Other vulnerabilities patched also include methods to bypass Factory Reset Protection, issues that could be exploited to allow denial of service attacks, and issues that allow code execution on devices with root. IT professionals will be happy to also see mail and ActiveSync issues that could allow access to "sensitive" information patched in this update.</p> <p>As always, Google also reminds us that there have been no reports of users being affected by these issues, and they have a recommended procedure to help prevent devices from falling victim to these and future issues:</p> <ul><li>Exploitation for many issues on Android is made more difficult by enhancements in newer versions of the Android platform. We encourage all users to update to the latest version of Android where possible.</li> <li>The Android Security team is actively monitoring for abuse with Verify Apps and SafetyNet, which will warn the user about detected potentially harmful applications about to be installed. Device rooting tools are prohibited within Google Play. To protect users who install applications from outside of Google Play, Verify Apps is enabled by default and will warn users about known rooting applications. Verify Apps attempts to identify and block installation of known malicious applications that exploit a privilege escalation vulnerability. If such an application has already been installed, Verify Apps will notify the user and attempt to remove any such applications.</li> <li>As appropriate, Google Hangouts and Messenger applications do not automatically pass media to processes such as mediaserver.</li> </ul><h2>Regarding issues mentioned in the previous bulletin</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/android-april-2-security-patch-live-here-are-details-you-need-know' title="The Android April 2 security patch is live - here are the details you need to know"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2016/02/nexus-update.jpg?itok=kceaQD2w' /></a></p> <p>On March 18, 2016 Google issued <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/critical-security-flaw-found-android-patch-coming-nexus-devices-few-days">a separate supplemental security bulletin</a> about issues in the Linux kernel used on many Android phones and tablets. It was demonstrated that an exploit in versions 3.4, 3.10 and 3.14 of the Linux kernel used in Android allowed devices to be permanently compromised — rooted, in other words — and affected phones and other devices would require a re-flash of the operating system to recover. Because an application was able to demonstrate this exploit, a mid-month bulletin was released. Google also mentioned that Nexus devices would receive a patch "within a few days." That patch never materialized, and Google makes no mention of why in the latest security bulletin.</p> <p>The issue — CVE-2015-1805 — has been patched completely in the April 2, 2016 security update. AOSP branches for Android versions 4.4.4, 5.0.2, 5.1.1, 6.0, and 6.0.1 have received this patch, and the rollout to the source is in progress.</p> <p>Google also mentions that devices that may have received a patch dated April 1, 2016 have not been patched against this particular exploit, and only Android devices with a patch level dated April 2, 2016 or later are current.</p> <p>The update sent to the <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/samsungs-galaxy-s6-verizon-wireless-first-get-april-security-patch">Verizon Galaxy S6 and Galaxy S6 edge</a> is dated April 2, 2016 and <em>does</em> contain these fixes.</p> <p>The update sent to the <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/t-mobile-rolling-out-update-galaxy-s7">T-Mobile Galaxy S7 and Galaxy S7 edge</a> is dated April 2, 2016 and <em>does</em> contain these fixes.</p> <p>Build AAE298 for unlocked BlackBerry Priv phones is dated April 2, 2016 and <em>does</em> contain these fixes. It was released in late March, 2016.</p> <p>Phones running a 3.18 kernel version are unaffected by this particular issue, but still require the patches for other issues addressed in the April 2, 2016 patch.</p> </div></div></div><br clear='all'/><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/a2.htm"><img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/></a><img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386644504/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/><img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/5q4DSLnJX_Q" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Jerry Hildenbrand</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb5b324/sc/23/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Candroid0Eapril0E20Esecurity0Epatch0Elive0Ehere0Eare0Edetails0Eyou0Eneed0Eknow/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best music player apps for Android</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/NriluaQVDoc/story01.htm</link>
      <description>Get the best music experience on your Android phone or tablet with these great apps Over the years music fans have gradually changed how they listen to their music, and what they listen to it on. With the rise of the smartphone it's only natural that now the one device we carry with us everywhere is also our primary media player. On Android, we're also fortunate that there's a huge community of developers that create apps that can better the experience we're provided by the folks who made our phones. The Google Play Store has many music related apps to choose from, but some do stand out from the crowd. It'd be impossible to look at all of them, so here we've chosen some that we think are some of the best there is. Let's take a look. Article updated April 2016. Poweramp Poweramp is a real favorite. It offers a list of features long enough that we could sit here talking about it all day. But, if you're serious about your music, you should definitely take a look. Making that e...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 17:23:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36927 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"><div class="field-items"><div class="field-item even"><p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2015/01/podcast-event.jpg?itok=zsMimlTM' /></a></p> <p class="intro">Get the best music experience on your Android phone or tablet with these great apps</p> <p>Over the years music fans have gradually changed how they listen to their music, and what they listen to it on. With the rise of the smartphone it's only natural that now the one device we carry with us everywhere is also our primary media player. On Android, we're also fortunate that there's a huge community of developers that create apps that can better the experience we're provided by the folks who made our phones.</p> <p>The <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./google-play-store" title="Google Play Store">Google Play Store</a> has many music related apps to choose from, but some do stand out from the crowd. It'd be impossible to look at all of them, so here we've chosen some that we think are some of the best there is. Let's take a look.</p> <p class="update">Article updated April 2016.</p> <p><!--break--> </p> <h2>Poweramp</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2015/11/poweramp-nexus-6p.jpg?itok=tIztj-tg' /></a></p> <p>Poweramp is a real favorite. It offers a list of features long enough that we could sit here talking about it all day. But, if you're serious about your music, you should definitely take a look. Making that easier is the free 15-day trial. No barriers, just full access for that 15-days to see whether you like it or not.</p> <p>And the chances are pretty high that you will like it. It has a much different visual look to something like DoubleTwist, but looks just as fantastic in its own way. Big album artwork in the "Now Playing" view, a crisp and clean layout and some pretty amazing customizations. Poweramp supports themes and has a bunch of tweaks you can make in the settings, so you can really create the music player you've always wanted.</p> <p>With a ton of different files supported, a view to look through your folders, an equalizer, crossfade, gapless, and much, much more, Poweramp is definitely one of the best music players on Android.</p> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2015/11/poweramp-screens.jpg?itok=6tcGL6RF' /></a></p> <p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.maxmpz.audioplayer" title="" class="cta large">Download Poweramp (Free Trial)</a></p> <h2>DoubleTwist Cloudplayer</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2015/11/doubletwist-cloudplayer.jpg?itok=cnjFedu0' /></a></p> <p>We've talked about <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./doubletwist" title="DoubleTwist">DoubleTwist</a> a lot around these parts and with good reason. DoubleTwist became a favorite of Android users that had deep roots in the iTunes ecosystem, and still is. The base app has been replaced on this list by Cloudplayer, a newer offering that looks great and has hooks into some of the most popular cloud storage services to deliver your music.</p> <p>We're not talking about hooking into streaming services, either. Create your own cloud streaming library with your own music, a Dropbox, OneDrive or Google Drive account and DoubleTwist Cloudplayer. Access to these is unlockable via an in-app purchase, but the basic app is free. And the basic app will also play your lossless FLAC files.</p> <p>That in-app purchase also unlocks Chromecast and AirPlay support and the equaliser tools to help you get the most from your music. And like the older app you can still use it to listen to radio and podcasts, too, as well as now having support for both Android Wear and Android Auto. A pretty well stocked one stop shop for all your audio needs.</p> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2015/11/doubletwist-cloudplayer-screens.jpg?itok=Gk_BXI9T' /></a></p> <p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.doubleTwist.cloudPlayer" title="" class="cta large">Download DoubleTwist Cloudplayer (Free with in-app purchases)</a></p> <h2>Google Play Music</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2015/11/play-music-nexus-6p.jpg?itok=r5McuAMH' /></a></p> <p>Not <strong>just</strong> a music player, but we have to include <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/tag/google-play-music" title="Google Play Music">Google Play Music</a>. While it doesn't have the deep customization or power features of something like Poweramp, it offers what many others do not; that huge cloud library for your own music. After all, without the music to listen too, what good is a killer music player?</p> <p>That's not to say Google Play Music isn't a good music player, because it is. Being a Google product it integrates perfectly with your device – including the sweet lockscreen artwork. But the real value is in that cloud storage. It means you can take your music collection with you on whichever Android and iOS device you own. Sure, you need to offline some of that from time-to-time, but it's always with you.</p> <p>Google also has its own store and streaming service built into the same app making it a superb one stop shop for all your musical needs. What it lacks in features compared to others it makes up for in convenience.</p> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2015/11/gpm-screens-fixed.jpg?itok=FqJSU-Zz' /></a></p> <p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.music" title="" class="cta large">Download Google Play Music (Free)</a></p> <h2>Shuttle Music Player</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2015/11/shuttle-player-nexus-6p.jpg?itok=XmYYrddA' /></a></p> <p>Shuttle is perhaps one you've not heard of before, but one that's definitely worth your attention. Where something like Poweramp is pretty heavy duty and has tons of settings and customizations, Shuffle offers a portion of that with a much more lightweight look and feel.</p> <p>It comes with a sleep timer, gapless playback, a choice of a few different themes, built in equalizer and much more. And for the Materiyolo kids out there, it's pretty much perfect in how it looks. It comes in free and paid versions, but with the paid version just $0.99, it also represents fantastic value for money.</p> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2015/11/shuttle-screens.jpg?itok=Tq7g-x96' /></a></p> <p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=another.music.player" title="" class="cta large">Download Shuttle Music Player (free)</a></p> <h2>Equalizer+</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2015/11/equalizer-nexus-6p.jpg?itok=jKI_LTwJ' /></a></p> <p>The clue to a big part of this app is in the name. As with the other apps mentioned in this post, there's a pretty decent Equalizer built into this one. It's also a pretty solid music player, though to take advantage of everything it offers you will need to put your hand in your wallet.</p> <p>On offer though is that 5-band equalizer with presets, bass booster, contextual search, a visualizer – which can be displayed on a second screen – fade and much more. The app is free to download, and you get access to the main equalizer controls for that, too.</p> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2015/11/equalizer-screens.jpg?itok=cGgUmdE1' /></a></p> <p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.djit.equalizerplusforandroidfree" title="" class="cta large">Download Equalizer (free with in-app purchases)</a></p> <h2>Amazon Music</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2015/11/amazon-music-nexus-6p.jpg?itok=Wulkg37p' /></a></p> <p>Google isn't the only provider on Android offering an all-in-one store, cloud and player solution. Amazon has its own thing going on and combines its Prime Music streaming service with its music store and a decent looking music player all in one. If you're a <a href="http://www.amazon.com/Amazon-Prime-One-Year-Membership/dp/B00DBYBNEE?m2k=d_ac&amp;tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" rel="nofollow">Prime subscriber</a> in selected markets you'll have Prime Music and so you'll need this on your phone. Amazon also offers you a cloud locker, much like Google, to access music you already own on any of your devices, and the app will play anything you have stored locally.</p> <p>It doesn't offer some of the techy stuff that audio nerds will find in some other apps on this list but it does give you lyrics. Sing along while you're on the bus to work!</p> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2015/11/amazon-music-screens.jpg?itok=vSyX8FUS' /></a></p> <p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.amazon.mp3" title="" class="cta large">Download Amazon Music</a></p> <h2>GoneMAD Music Player</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2015/11/gonemad-nexus-6p_0.jpg?itok=l2v6idPU' /></a></p> <p>GoneMAD boasts over 250 customizations, so needless to say we're not going to talk about them all, here. Add to this over 1000 themes and what you've got is a music app that really can be tailored to suit your own personal tastes. On the techy front it boasts gapless playback, support for a whole bunch of formats including lossless audio, smart playlists, an equalizer, multi-window and much, much more. You can even go back to the old UI if you don't like how it looks right now.</p> <p>The app is free to download for 14-days and after that if you like it and want to keep using it, you'll need to buy the full version. And you might just want to do that.</p> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2015/11/gonemad-music-screens.jpg?itok=MNeBvfTe' /></a></p> <p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=gonemad.gmmp" title="" class="cta large">Download GoneMAD Music Player (Free trial)</a></p> <h2>Rocket Music Player</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2015/11/rocketplayer-nexus-6p.jpg?itok=YkPdWg5I' /></a></p> <p>Rocket is another hugely popular music player for Android with a bunch of good reasons to choose it. You've got a stylish minimalism mixed with a 5-band equalizer, folders support, Chromecast, video and podcasts and much much more.</p> <p>That's just in the free app. If you upgrade to Premium you also get a bunch of different themes, support for lossless audio, a 10-band equalizer and a whole bundle of other features to perfect your audio experience.</p> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-music-players-android' title="The best music player apps for Android"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2015/11/rocketplayer-screens.jpg?itok=f9jndbSj' /></a></p> <p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.jrtstudio.AnotherMusicPlayer" title="" class="cta large">Download Rocket Music Player (Free)</a></p> <h2>Your picks?</h2> <p>So, that's five of what we think are the best music players Android has to offer, but what about you? If you've a particular favorite you wish to share, drop it and why you like it so much into the comments below!</p> </div></div></div><br clear='all'/><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/a2.htm"><img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/a2.img" border="0"/></a><img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386673066/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/a2t.img" border="0"/><img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/mf.gif' border='0'/><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/NriluaQVDoc" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Richard Devine</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb552ae/sc/28/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Cbest0Emusic0Eplayers0Eandroid/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google is updating its Play family of apps with a unified icon design</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/87fjr0kz4Aw/story01.htm</link>
      <description>Google has announced that it will be rolling out a new set of icons to its Play family of apps. The suite of apps includes Google Play, Play Store, Play Movies &amp;amp; TV, Play Music, Play Games, Play Books and Play Newsstand. All of the icons now have the same triangular design so at a glance they look similar, yet they each feature a distinction to make it easy to recognize the app. From Google's announcement: Since launching Google Play four years ago, we've always had dedicated apps in addition to the Google Play store. Today, all our icons are getting an update to provide a consistent look across the entire family of Play apps. You'll start to see the new Google Play icons across devices and online in the coming weeks. We hope you'll continue enjoying the Play family of products—now with a new look. Be sure to keep an eye out for the new icons to appear on your devices. What are your thoughts on the changes? Let us know in the comments! ...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb552af/sc/15/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 17:18:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53434 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"><div class="field-items"><div class="field-item even"><p>Google has announced that it will be rolling out a new set of icons to its Play family of apps. The suite of apps includes <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./google-play">Google Play</a>, Play Store, Play Movies &amp; TV, Play Music, Play Games, Play Books and Play Newsstand. All of the icons now have the same triangular design so at a glance they look similar, yet they each feature a distinction to make it easy to recognize the app. <!--break--></p> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/google-updating-its-play-family-apps-unified-icon-design' title="Google is updating its Play family of apps with a unified icon design"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2016/04/google_play_icons_blogpost.png?itok=F3QAZw2k' /></a></p> <p>From <a href="http://officialandroid.blogspot.com/2016/04/a-new-look-for-google-play-family-of-apps.html">Google's announcement</a>:</p> <blockquote> <p>Since launching Google Play four years ago, we've always had dedicated apps in addition to the Google Play store. Today, all our icons are getting an update to provide a consistent look across the entire family of Play apps.</p> <p>You'll start to see the new Google Play icons across devices and online in the coming weeks. We hope you'll continue enjoying the Play family of products—now with a new look.</p> </blockquote> <p>Be sure to keep an eye out for the new icons to appear on your devices. What are your thoughts on the changes? Let us know in the comments!</p> </div></div></div><br clear='all'/><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/a2.htm"><img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/a2.img" border="0"/></a><img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386673065/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb552af/sc/15/a2t.img" border="0"/><img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb552af/sc/15/mf.gif' border='0'/><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/87fjr0kz4Aw" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Jared DiPane</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb552af/sc/15/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Cgoogle0Eupdating0Eits0Eplay0Efamily0Eapps0Eunified0Eicon0Edesign/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Android keyboard apps</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/gX9h-7n0dM4/story01.htm</link>
      <description>Tap tap tap away with these great keyboards for your Android phones and tablets. Keyboards are important. Really important. Without a good keyboard, communicating on a smartphone can go from heavenly bliss straight back to teeth-pulling torture. Keyboards are also one of the most important apps you select from a security standpoint, as they are by their very nature keyloggers. And while most users will never really need to worry about if their keyboard is stealing their emails and passwords as they type it in, it is something that you should keep in mind if you're checking out a keyboard that you know absolutely nothing about. There are a number of great keyboards out there, each with its own features, flaws, and followings. There are utterly simplistic keyboards and bleeding-edge keyboards with a longer list of features than some smartphones. Finding a keyboard that fits you and your lifestyle can be a bit daunting. Whatever your style may be, these are the five keyboards that we...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 16:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43976 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"><div class="field-items"><div class="field-item even"><p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-android-keyboard' title="The best Android keyboard apps"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_blw/public/article_images/2015/01/best-keyboards-hero.jpg?itok=HjF40bRj' /></a></p> <p class="intro">Tap tap tap away with these great keyboards for your Android phones and tablets.</p> <p>Keyboards are important. Really important. Without a good keyboard, communicating on a smartphone can go from heavenly bliss straight back to teeth-pulling torture. Keyboards are also one of the most important apps you select from a <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/look-application-permissions">security standpoint</a>, as they are by their very nature keyloggers. And while most users will never really need to worry about if their keyboard is stealing their emails and passwords as they type it in, it is something that you should keep in mind if you're checking out a keyboard that you know absolutely nothing about.</p> <p>There are a number of great keyboards out there, each with its own features, flaws, and followings. There are utterly simplistic keyboards and bleeding-edge keyboards with a longer list of features than some smartphones. Finding a keyboard that fits you and your lifestyle can be a bit daunting.</p> <p>Whatever your style may be, these are the five keyboards that we think stand above the rest, and may be worthy of composing your LOLs and WTFs.</p> <p class="update">Article updated April 2016</p> <p><!--break--> </p> <h2 data-title="SwiftKey">SwiftKey</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-android-keyboard' title="The best Android keyboard apps"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2015/01/swiftkey-best-keyboards.jpg?itok=T37k1wEe' /></a></p> <p>If you had to ask us to pick one keyboard as our ultimate top choice for Android, SwiftKey would be it.</p> <p>For years, SwiftKey soared above Google's included keyboard, and it did — and still does — come preinstalled on many a phone and tablet. SwiftKey's prediction methods, called the "fluency engine," has made it the keyboard that many users and editors alike keep coming back to. SwiftKey has been pre-loaded on millions of devices over the years, including on flagships like the Samsung Galaxy S4.</p> <p>While SwiftKey used to be a paid app, the keyboard itself went free in 2014, instead having its users pay for themes — such as their <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/new-swiftkey-themes-bring-frozen-crew-your-keyboard">Frozen theme pack</a>. SwiftKey has led the keyboard pack for a while, but it has plenty of competition to keep it on its toes. .</p> <p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.touchtype.swiftkey" title="" class="cta large slides-only">Download SwiftKey</a></p> <h2 data-title="Swype">Swype</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-android-keyboard' title="The best Android keyboard apps"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_blw/public/article_images/2015/01/Swype-hero-motox.jpg?itok=0CUBECYD' /></a></p> <p><a href="www.androidcentral.com/app/swype">Swype</a> is to SwiftKey as GM is to Ford. Both are established, respected, feature-rich keyboards. Swype allows you to swipe out words or whole sentences, and Swype supports typing in two languages at once, for bilingual users. Swype offers a free version, but the full version is a dollar, and themes are an additional two dollars apiece. For those uninterested in having Elsa on they keyboard, Swype offers sports themes, including Major League Soccer themes.</p> <p>Swype ties into Android's Accessibility features for TalkBack and Explore By Touch, which make Swype a keyboard vision-impaired users can learn more easily on their own. Copy/Cut/Paste functions are embedded as gestures in Swype's keyboard, too. Swype all the things!</p> <p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.nuance.swype.dtc" title="" class="cta large slides-only">Download Swype</a></p> <h2 data-title="Google Keyboard">Google Keyboard</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-android-keyboard' title="The best Android keyboard apps"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_blw/public/article_images/2014/11/google-keyboard-material-n5-hero.jpg?itok=mdCLn7fl' /></a></p> <p>While years ago, Google's built-in android keyboard was considered a bit of a slouch, it's built to compete today. The <a href="www.androidcentral.com/tag/google-keyboard">Google Keyboard</a> is completely free, supports gesture typing for both individual words and entire sentences, a bounty of languages, a modest choice of themes, and it was the first keyboard to feature the full library of Kit Kat emoji last year. That may not sound like much, but after years of mediocre or downright dreadful emoji from the OEMs and keyboard manufacturers, Kit Kat system emoji was a welcome change and drew in quite a few users before third-party keyboards began to integrate it.</p> <p>The Google Keyboard employs Google's own text-to-speech engine for voice dictation, and the many advancements in voice recognition made for Google Now and Android Wear over the last few years have benefitted this keyboard greatly. Google's keyboard still has a little ways to go on the text prediction, but it does learn from your typed data across Google's apps and services.</p> <p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.inputmethod.latin" title="" class="cta large slides-only">Download Google Keyboard</a></p> <h2 data-title="Fleksy">Fleksy</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-android-keyboard' title="The best Android keyboard apps"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_blw/public/article_images/2014/12/fleksy-keyboard-m8-hero.jpg?itok=DL7h-c9k' /></a></p> <p>Fleksy is a keyboard that exudes class with its minimalist styling and its artfully done themes — if you want a Frozen keyboard theme that actually looks good, go get the Fleksy one. Now, make no mistake, Fleksy is not a cheap keyboard, though they do offer a 30-day trial to decide if it's worth the $1.99. After paying for the keyboard, most premium themes are also paid, including licensed themes like Frozen and The Hunger Games.</p> <p>Beyond more traditional customization options like a fifth row for numbers and support for more layouts than your standard QWERTY and DVORAK, Fleksy's keyboard has extensions, allowing it to send things like gifs or work while becoming invisible. Another interesting addition to Fleksy is are the badges and rewards system that encourages users to master the keyboard and its features.</p> <p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.syntellia.fleksy.keyboard" title="" class="cta large slides-only">Download Fleksy</a></p> <h2 data-title="Touchpal">Touchpal</h2> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/best-android-keyboard' title="The best Android keyboard apps"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_blw/public/article_images/2014/12/touchpal-AOTY2014.jpg?itok=1sQtVLXv' /></a></p> <p>TouchPal is one of the lesser-recognized keyboards out there, but a few useful features have helped it stand out and get over 10 million installs. TouchPal's keyboard held the freemium model of an always-free keyboard with a paid theme store and paid cloud syncing before SwiftKey and the rest of the field headed that direction. However, while you can pay for premium themes, you also have the option to simply upload your own background image and make your own for free.</p> <p>What has stood out about TouchPal for me, and made it my primary keyboard for the last year now are three things: the dialogue between the developers and the <a href="https://plus.google.com/u/0/communities/105746648636072214666">beta community</a>, swiping from the backspace to delete the last word, and swiping the space bar up to access the emoji drawer, which supports system emoji and now emoji art and emoticons.</p> <p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.cootek.smartinputv5&amp;hl=en" title="" class="cta large slides-only">Download TouchPal</a></p> <h3>Which keyboard do you use?</h3> <p></p><center> <script type="text/javascript" charset="utf-8" src="http://static.polldaddy.com/p/8595140.js"></script><noscript><a href="http://polldaddy.com/poll/8595140/">What keyboard do you use?</a></noscript> </center> <p></p> <p>So, which keyboard graces your device? Do you prefer a more simplistic keyboard or a model with more bells and whistles? Chime in below in the comments section with your keyboard setup.</p> </div></div></div><br clear='all'/><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/a2.htm"><img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/></a><img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386643438/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/><img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/gX9h-7n0dM4" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Ara Wagoner</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb5ae2a/sc/23/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Cbest0Eandroid0Ekeyboard/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Echo Dot review: An inch and a half of Alexa may be all you need</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/nKi3mcnGTyc/story01.htm</link>
      <description>The cliche is true — good things can come in small packages. Don't overthink the Amazon Echo Dot — particularly if you already know Alexa. Echo Dot is what you get if you lop off the top inch and a half of an Echo. You keep the brains, of course — the voice recognition that makes Echo so powerful and Alexa so friendly. You keep the connected nature of the device — it still connects to Wifi. But you lose the decent speaker that make up the other seven inches of the Echo. And ... That's it, folks. That's Amazon Echo Dot. It's a much smaller Alexa-powered connected device that does everything its big sister does. OK, there's a little more to it. Here's our Amazon Echo Dot review. About this review We're writing this review after a few days with the Amazon Echo Dot, which we purchased. While generally we'd say that's nowhere near enough to review something like a smartphone, Echo Dot essentially is a smaller Amazon Echo, which we've reviewed not just once, but twice...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 15:00:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53395 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"><div class="field-items"><div class="field-item even"><p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/amazon-echo-dot-review' title="Amazon Echo Dot review: An inch and a half of Alexa may be all you need"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2016/04/amazon-echo-dot-14new.jpg?itok=Uz4Nra03' /></a></p> <p class="intro">The cliche is true — good things can come in small packages.</p> <p>Don't overthink the Amazon Echo Dot — particularly if you already know Alexa. Echo Dot is what you get if you lop off the top inch and a half of an Echo. You keep the brains, of course — the voice recognition that makes Echo so powerful and Alexa so friendly. You keep the connected nature of the device — it still connects to Wifi. But you lose the decent speaker that make up the other seven inches of the Echo.</p> <p>And ... That's it, folks. That's Amazon Echo Dot. It's a much smaller Alexa-powered connected device that does everything its big sister does.</p> <p>OK, there's a little more to it. Here's our Amazon Echo Dot review. <!--break--></p> <h2>About <em>this review</em></h2> <p class="award"><img src="http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/article_images/2015/10/choice-award-ac.png" alt="Android Central Choice Award" class="left" width="150px" /></p> <p>We're writing this review after a few days with the Amazon Echo Dot, which we purchased. While generally we'd say that's nowhere near enough to review something like a smartphone, Echo Dot essentially is a smaller <a href="http://www.amazon.com/Amazon-SK705DI-Echo/dp/B00X4WHP5E/?tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" rel="nofollow">Amazon Echo</a>, which we've reviewed <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/amazon-echo-review">not just once</a>, but <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/amazon-echo-review-sequel">twice</a> over the past year or so.</p> <p>There's not a whole lot to figure out there. Nothing really subjective to get a feel for.</p> <p>I've used it in a bedroom. I've used it in an office. I've used it a kitchen. My kids are fighting over who gets to have it in which room.</p> <div id="Review_BTF_1-wrap" class="netshelter-ad gpt"> <div class="netshelter-ad-inner"><div class="adunit" id="div-gpt-ad-Review_BTF_1"></div></div> </div> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/amazon-echo-dot-review' title="Amazon Echo Dot review: An inch and a half of Alexa may be all you need"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2016/04/amazon-echo-dot-9.jpg?itok=2fLrSJKv' /></a></p> <h4 class="micro">Awwwwww, it's a baby Echo</h4> <h2>Amazon Echo Dot <em>hardware</em></h2> <p>Amazon Echo is nine inches of black, cylindrical speaker. It's not huge, but it's sizable. Echo Dot is not. And it's tempting to think that a smaller Echo isn't as capable. But Alexa hasn't lost her smarts at all. In fact, that's maybe the most important thing to remember about Echo. It's the rare product that you can buy today, knowing that it actually <em>will</em> get better over time. Nary a week goes by where Amazon doesn't add some new under-the-hood functionality. (And the best part that it's done entirely without you having to manually update the Echo.) Echo gets smarter. Echo Dot gets smarter.</p> <p>It's got the exact same look and feel as the full size Echo. Same LED ring at the top (though ours has a little bit of sharp edge) that glows orange during setup (which takes all of 1 minute to do) and blue when Alexa is doing her thing. (It's also a part of the volume ring.) You've still got the mute and action buttons. New this time around, however, are a microUSB port for charging, and a 3.5mm jack for audio out. There's still a built-in speaker, too, but the end result is more the quality of what you get in smartphone. (Which makes sense in this case.)</p> <p>Also new is the ability to steam audio <em>out</em> from the Echo Dot via Bluetooth to another speaker.</p> <p>So you've got three options when it comes to how good Echo dot sounds.</p> <ul><li>The tinny, built-in speaker. Works fine. Won't impress anyone. But doesn't take up any additional space.</li> <li>Use the 3.5mm jack to plug in to another speaker. But that means more wires all in once place. Or maybe into a receiver — but that requires being on the right input, and then you'll have Alexa getting piped through a full stereo system.</li> <li>Bluetooth over to another speaker. </li> </ul><p>The bottom of the Echo Dot has that rubberized footing that keeps things in place when you're turning the volume ring — though you could just, you know, ask Alexa to raise or lower the volume. The power LED on the back, 4-foot audio cable and 5-foot microUSB cable make up the rest of the hardware.</p> <p><a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/definitive-guide-amazon-prime-benefits" title="" class="cta large">More: Why you should sign up for Amazon Prime</a></p> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/amazon-echo-dot-review' title="Amazon Echo Dot review: An inch and a half of Alexa may be all you need"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2016/04/amazon-echo-dot.jpg?itok=5t8ynlng' /></a></p> <h4 class="micro">Let's talk ...</h4> <h2>Amazon Echo Dot <em>software</em></h2> <p>There's not a whole lot to say about software for Echo Dot, either. You'll set it up via the Alexa app (available <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.amazon.dee.app">on Android</a> as well as <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/amazon-alexa/id944011620?mt=8&amp;at=10l3Vy&amp;ct=d_ac" title="" rel="nofollow">on iOS</a>. (And your Echo Dot is waiting for you in the app already, because Amazon is smart and went ahead and added it to your Amazon account, which you use to log in to the app.) It's the exact same app you use for Amazon Echo. It's great at walking you through the brief Wifi Direct setup process to hook into Wifi, and then that's it. You can use the Alexa App as a companion if you want — and it's fun to see it update with information in real time as you talk to her. You can manage timers and alarms and music and books and your smart home connections.</p> <p>Or you don't have to do any of that. I've had an Echo for more than a year now and almost never open the app. Once you get a feel for what Alexa can do, it really does become that sort of pseudo-personal relationship. It's sort of a matter of how much you use your Echo — and <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/why-amazon-echo-one-connected-device-you-should-buy">this is how I tend to use it</a>).</p> <p>On its own, it's damned powerful. And it only gets better if you actually use the app alongside it.</p> <p>But Alexa isn't perfect. If you've used an Echo for any length of time you'll pretty quickly realize that she's smart, but not brilliant. She struggles with obscure questions far faster than Google Now does. Ask Alexa how long it'll take to drive to, say, Los Angeles, and she'll give you the distance. Google actually answers the question.</p> <p>On the other hand, Google Now kinda sucks at adding things to your Amazon cart. Or playing back from Amazon Music on demand.</p> <p>And perhaps most important: I can ask Alexa to "Play the Android Central Podcast," and she'll <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/podcast">fire up the latest episode</a> via TuneIn. No downloading any other apps, no having to subscribe to feeds. It just plays in all its podcast glory. (Maybe that'll change when Google <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/podcasts-are-coming-google-play-music-podcasters-can-upload-episodes-now.">adds podcasts to Google Play Music</a></p> <div class="media-gallery-wrap"><div class="media-gallery-flat"><div data-title="Amazon Echo Dot" data-big="/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/xlarge_wm_brw/public/article_images/2016/04/amazon-echo-dot-13.jpg?itok=58ZjBdeW" class="flat-img " style="background-image:url(/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/w800h450crop/public/article_images/2016/04/amazon-echo-dot-13.jpg?itok=58ZjBdeW);"></div><div data-title="Amazon Echo Dot" data-big="/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/xlarge_wm_brw/public/article_images/2016/04/amazon-echo-dot-12.jpg?itok=l6okeAlS" class="flat-img " style="background-image:url(/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/w800h450crop/public/article_images/2016/04/amazon-echo-dot-12.jpg?itok=l6okeAlS);"></div><div data-title="Amazon Echo Dot" data-big="/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/xlarge_wm_brw/public/article_images/2016/04/amazon-echo-dot-7.jpg?itok=AZ1uJ8hp" class="flat-img " style="background-image:url(/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/w800h450crop/public/article_images/2016/04/amazon-echo-dot-7.jpg?itok=AZ1uJ8hp);"></div><div data-title="Amazon Echo Dot" data-big="/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/xlarge_wm_brw/public/article_images/2016/04/amazon-echo-dot-11.jpg?itok=es3heuGE" class="flat-img " style="background-image:url(/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/w800h450crop/public/article_images/2016/04/amazon-echo-dot-11.jpg?itok=es3heuGE);"></div><div data-title="Amazon Echo Dot" data-big="/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/xlarge_wm_brw/public/article_images/2016/04/amazon-echo-dot-7.jpg?itok=AZ1uJ8hp" class="flat-img " style="background-image:url(/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/w800h450crop/public/article_images/2016/04/amazon-echo-dot-7.jpg?itok=AZ1uJ8hp);"></div></div> <!--/media-gallery-flat--></div> <h4 class="micro">Shut up and take less of my money</h4> <h2>The bottom line: <em>Buy this!</em></h2> <p>Like we said at the outset, there's not a lot to figure out with the Echo Dot. It's a smaller Echo, with additional Bluetooth and 3.5 connections for external speakers, should you want something more than the tinny built-in speaker. Functionally, it's exactly the same as the full-size Echo — and just as good. It's just as responsive across the room as its larger, older sibling. it just doesn't sound as good out of the box.</p> <p>But on the other hand it's only $89 — some $90 less than <a href="http://www.amazon.com/Amazon-SK705DI-Echo/dp/B00X4WHP5E/?tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" rel="nofollow">the full-size Echo</a>. That's a pretty good price for Alexa, especially if you've got an old speaker laying around that you want to put to good use.</p> <p><a href="http://www.amazon.com/b/?node=14047587011&amp;tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" class="cta shop" rel="nofollow">Amazon Echo Dot</a></p> <div class="closeup bg-image" style="background-image: url('http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/article_images/2015/02/echo-background-13.jpg')"><div class="left extra"> <h3>Want an Echo Dot? There's a catch</h3> <p>Amazon Echo is way cool. And the idea of a smaller, cheaper Echo is one a lot of folks can get behind. But there's a catch. Just as Echo was difficult to purchase at first — the waiting list was quite long — you can't just go to Amazon, add an Echo Dot to your cart and have it the next day. First, you have to <a href="http://go.redirectingat.com/?id=23432X820453&amp;site=%20imore.com&amp;xs=1&amp;isjs=1&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB00DBYBNEE%3Fm1k%3Dmbnx107-20%26tag%3Dmbnx107-20%26t%3Dmbnx107-20%26m2k%3Dmbnx107-20%26mnsid%3Dmbnx107-20&amp;xguid=548f3a3a5702dbc59e4566f841384566&amp;xuuid=614c12a21e57c546b00abc2c82cba709&amp;xsessid=&amp;xcreo=0&amp;xed=0&amp;sref=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.androidcentral.com%2Fdefinitive-guide-amazon-prime-benefits&amp;pref=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.androidcentral.com%2Famazon-prime&amp;xtz=300">be an Amazon Prime member</a>. Then you'll need to use your voice to order a Dot either <a href="http://www.amazon.com/Amazon-SK705DI-Echo/dp/B00X4WHP5E/?qid=1459634548&amp;sr=8-1&amp;keywords=amazon+echo&amp;tag=androidcentralb-20&amp;m1k=d_ac" title="" rel="nofollow">from an Echo</a>, or through Amazon Fire TV or the Amazon app. (In other words, you can't just go to the website.)</p> <p>Echo Dot also isn't really in mass production yet — current shipping times after the initial wave are now in late July.</p> </div></div> </div></div></div><br clear='all'/><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/a2.htm"><img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/a2.img" border="0"/></a><img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386642460/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/a2t.img" border="0"/><img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/mf.gif' border='0'/><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/nKi3mcnGTyc" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Phil Nickinson</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb5a9ea/sc/28/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Camazon0Eecho0Edot0Ereview/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can now sign up for the BlackBerry Priv Marshmallow beta</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/gXXeSZE9_Ho/story01.htm</link>
      <description>As rumored, BlackBerry has announced the Marshmallow beta test for the BlackBerry Priv. You can now sign up to join the program, and the company will accept registrations for two weeks. The first wave will only be available to those who purchased their devices from Amazon, ShopBlackBerry or Carphone Warehouse. Spaces will be limited, and BlackBerry will begin pushing the beta out in the second week of April. If you want to sign up to test, you can do so at the link below. The program may show as full, but be sure to sign up for the waitlist so that when more spots open next week you may be able to get one. Sign up for the Marshmallow beta test ...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 14:55:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53427 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"><div class="field-items"><div class="field-item even"><p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/you-can-now-sign-blackberry-priv-marshmallow-beta' title="You can now sign up for the BlackBerry Priv Marshmallow beta"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2016/03/blackberry-priv-marshmallow.jpg?itok=v_Szsm91' /></a></p> <p>As rumored, <a href="http://blogs.blackberry.com/2016/04/help-put-android-marshmallow-on-priv-by-joining-our-beta-program/">BlackBerry has announced the Marshmallow beta</a> test for the <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./blackberry-priv">BlackBerry Priv</a>. You can now sign up to join the program, and the company will accept registrations for two weeks. The first wave will only be available to those who purchased their devices from Amazon, ShopBlackBerry or Carphone Warehouse. <!--break--></p> <p>Spaces will be limited, and BlackBerry will begin pushing the beta out in the second week of April. If you want to sign up to test, you can do so at the link below. The program may show as full, but be sure to sign up for the waitlist so that when more spots open next week you may be able to get one.</p> <p><a href="https://www.blackberry.com/beta/android" title="" class="cta large">Sign up for the Marshmallow beta test</a></p> </div></div></div><br clear='all'/><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/a2.htm"><img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/></a><img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386642459/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/><img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/gXXeSZE9_Ho" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Jared DiPane</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb5a9eb/sc/23/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Cyou0Ecan0Enow0Esign0Eblackberry0Epriv0Emarshmallow0Ebeta/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-Mobile rolling update for Galaxy S7, S7 edge that includes April security patch</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/gHHsL4YMC4g/story01.htm</link>
      <description>We've received numerous reports that T-Mobile is rolling out an update for the Samsung Galaxy S7 and Galaxy S7 edge. The U.S. carrier is believed to be pushing the smartphone up to PC8, introducing some minor improvements and applying bug fixes. According to the software update notification, this most recent update includes the following: The stability of recording video has been improved. Overall device performance has been improved. Battery life has been optimized. The security of your device has been improved. The April security patch from Google is also on-board, which is a welcomed sight. Don't worry if you haven't yet received the update notification. You can check manually by heading to Settings &amp;gt; About device and then hit check for the updates. Have you received the PC8 update on your Galaxy S7 or Galaxy S7 edge? Let us know in the comments. Join the discussion on our forum Big thanks to everyone who tipped us! Samsung Galaxy S7 and S7 edge Galaxy S7 rev...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 11:53:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53423 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded>&lt;div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"&gt;&lt;div class="field-items"&gt;&lt;div class="field-item even"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/t-mobile-rolling-out-update-galaxy-s7' title="T-Mobile rolling update for Galaxy S7, S7 edge that includes April security patch"&gt;&lt;img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2016/03/galaxy-s7-box-left.jpg?itok=JiHNDLR9' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We've received numerous reports that T-Mobile is rolling out an update for the &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s7"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S7&lt;/a&gt; and Galaxy S7 edge. The U.S. carrier is believed to be pushing the smartphone up to &lt;strong&gt;PC8&lt;/strong&gt;, introducing some minor improvements and applying bug fixes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;!--break--&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/t-mobile-rolling-out-update-galaxy-s7' title="T-Mobile rolling update for Galaxy S7, S7 edge that includes April security patch"&gt;&lt;img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2016/04/tmo-gs7-update.jpg?itok=lQPrT6Ej' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/t-mobile-rolling-out-update-galaxy-s7' title="T-Mobile rolling update for Galaxy S7, S7 edge that includes April security patch"&gt;&lt;img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2016/04/t-mo-gs7-update-screenie.jpg?itok=kxvnuw3V' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to the software update notification, this most recent update includes the following:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The stability of recording video has been improved.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Overall device performance has been improved.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Battery life has been optimized.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The security of your device has been improved.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The April security patch from Google is also on-board, which is a welcomed sight. Don't worry if you haven't yet received the update notification. You can check manually by heading to &lt;em&gt;Settings &amp;gt; About device&lt;/em&gt; and then hit check for the updates.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Have you received the &lt;strong&gt;PC8&lt;/strong&gt; update on your Galaxy S7 or Galaxy S7 edge? Let us know in the comments.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://forums.androidcentral.com/samsung-galaxy-s7/663483-t-mobile-update-today.html" title="" class="cta large"&gt;Join the discussion on our forum&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Big thanks to everyone who tipped us!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="devicebox"&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s7"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S7 and S7 edge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;div class="video"&gt;&lt;div class="video_iframe"&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/wCpHEsi6NfA?rel=0&amp;amp;autoplay=0&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&amp;amp;controls=2&amp;amp;autohide=1&amp;amp;showinfo=0" width="680" height="383" class="video-filter video-youtube vf-wcphesi6nfa" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!--/video--&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s7-review?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Galaxy S7 review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s7-edge-review?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Galaxy S7 edge review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/samsung-galaxy-s7-edge-review-canadian-perspective?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Galaxy S7 edge with Exynos: A Canadian perspective&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/comparing-galaxy-s7-and-s7-edge-colors?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Here are all four Galaxy S7 colors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/galaxy-s7s-camera-drops-12mp-picks-14-micron-pixels-and-even-faster-focusing?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Details on the Galaxy S7's camera&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/galaxy-s7-regains-microsd-card-shuns-adoptable-storage?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;The SD card is back on the GS7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://forums.androidcentral.com/samsung-galaxy-s7/?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Join our Galaxy S7 forums&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/ext?link=http%3A%2F%2Fclick.linksynergy.com%2Ffs-bin%2Fclick%3Fid%3DJAF5WzpxbKM%26subid%3D%26offerid%3D321145.1%26type%3D10%26tmpid%3D13664%26u1%3Ddac%26RD_PARM1%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fwww.att.com%252Fcellphones%252Fsamsung%252Fgalaxy-s7.html" title="" class="buy-link" rel="nofollow"&gt;AT&amp;amp;T&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sprint.com/apps/new-samsung-galaxy-phone-offers/index.html" title="" class="buy-link"&gt;Sprint&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/ext?link=http%3A%2F%2Ft-mobile.7eer.net%2Fc%2F159229%2F187812%2F3290%3FsubId1%3Dd_ac%26subId2%3Dd_ac%26u%3Dhttp%253A%252F%252Fwww.t-mobile.com%252Fcell-phones%252Fsamsung-galaxy-s7.html" title="" class="buy-link" rel="nofollow"&gt;T-Mobile&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/ext?link=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.jdoqocy.com%2Fclick-7293382-11365093-1445520420000%3Fsid%3Dd_ac%26url%3Dhttp%253A%252F%252Fwww.verizonwireless.com%252Fsmartphones%252Fsamsung-galaxy-s7%252F" title="" class="buy-link" rel="nofollow"&gt;Verizon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div&gt; &lt;style&gt; &lt;!--/*--&gt;&lt;![CDATA[/* &gt;&lt;!--*/ &lt;!--/*--&gt;&lt;![CDATA[/* &gt;&lt;!--*/ &lt;!--/*--&gt;&lt;![CDATA[/* &gt;&lt;!--*/ /* ALL SIZES */ .devicebox { background: #fff; border: solid #000; border-width: 2px 0; box-sizing: border-box; margin: 0 auto 30px; overflow: auto; padding: 20px 0 15px; position: relative; } div .devicebox ul li, div .devicebox p { box-sizing: border-box; color: #000; display: table; font: 16px "Proxima Nova Th",helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; width: 100%; } .devicebox h3 { color: #000; font: 26px/0.9 "Proxima Nova Bold",helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; margin: 0 0 15px; text-transform: uppercase; } .devicebox a { color: #008099; } .devicebox .video { margin: 0 auto 15px; } .devicebox p { margin: 0px; } .devicebox p.list-head { font: 20px "Proxima Nova Bold",helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; padding: 0 15px; } .devicebox p img, .entry-content .devicebox p &gt; img { width: 100%; } .devicebox ul { display: table; margin: 0 0 10px; width: 100%; } .devicebox ul li { background: #f7f7f7; margin: 2px 0; padding: 4px 15px; } .devicebox ul li:hover { background: #fff; } .devicebox ul li:before { display: none; } .devicebox p ~ p { line-height: 1.25; } .devicebox p:first-of-type + p { padding: 15px; } .devicebox a.buy-link { border-radius: 5px; display: inline-block; font: 14px/31px "Proxima Nova Extrabld",Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; text-align: center; } .devicebox a.buy-link, .devicebox a.buy-link:link, .devicebox a.buy-link:active, .devicebox a.buy-link:visited { background: #37B5D7; color: #FFF; } .devicebox a.buy-link:hover { background: #2694B2; text-decoration: none; } .devicebox a.buy-link:before { content: "\e61e"; font: 40px/0 "ac_iconset" !important; margin: 0 3px 0 -8px; vertical-align: middle; } /* PORTRAIT */ div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) { float: right; margin: 0 0 20px 20px; max-width: 350px; width: 50%; } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox h3, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) h3 { text-align: center; } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) a.buy-link { margin: 0 5px 8px 0; width: calc(50% - 5px); } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(even), div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) .devicebox a.buy-link:last-child, div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(even), div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) .devicebox a.buy-link:last-child { margin-right: 0; } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child { display: block; margin-right: 0; width: auto; } /* LANDSCAPE */ @media all and (min-width: 1025px) { .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox { padding: 20px 0 25px; } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox .video, .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { float: left; margin: 0 30px 0 0; width: calc(100% - 375px); } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { bottom: 20px; display: block; overflow: hidden; position: absolute; top: 59px; } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p img, .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p &gt; img { position: absolute; top: 50%; transform: translateY(-50%); } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p, .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox ul { box-sizing: border-box; margin-left: calc(100% - 345px); width: 340px; } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p.list-head { margin-top: -5px; } } @media all and (min-width: 1025px), all and (max-width: 800px) and (min-width: 660px), all and (max-width: 500px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link { margin: 0 5px 8px 0; width: calc(50% - 5px); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(even), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:last-child { margin-right: 0; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child { display: block; width: auto; } } @media all and (max-width: 800px) and (min-width: 660px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox { padding: 20px 0 25px; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox .video, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { float: left; margin: 0 30px 0 0; width: calc(100% - 375px); } div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { bottom: 20px; display: block; overflow: hidden; position: absolute; top: 59px; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p img, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p &gt; img { position: absolute; top: 50%; transform: translateY(-50%); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox ul { box-sizing: border-box; margin-left: calc(100% - 345px); width: 340px; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p.list-head { margin-top: -5px; } } @media all and (max-width: 1024px) and (min-width: 801px), all and (max-width: 660px) and (min-width: 501px) { div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:before, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) a.buy-link:before { display: none; } } @media all and (max-width: 660px), all and (max-width: 1024px) and (min-width: 801px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 { text-align: center; } div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox ul, div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox p { display: block; } } @media all and (max-width: 660px) and (min-width: 501px), all and (max-width: 1024px) and (min-width: 801px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link { margin: 0 5px 8px 0; width: calc((100% / 3) - 7px); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n):nth-last-child(odd), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n):nth-last-child(n+3) { margin-right: 0; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(2), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(2) ~ a, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(4), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(4) ~ a { width: calc(50% - 5px); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(2) ~ a:nth-last-of-type(odd), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(4) ~ a:nth-last-of-type(odd) { margin-right: 0; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child { display: inline-block; } } @media all and (max-width: 800px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox { margin: 0 0 30px; max-width: none; width: auto; } } @media all and (max-width: 500px) { .devicebox, div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) { float: none; margin: 0 0 30px; max-width: none; width: auto; } .devicebox a.buy-link:before { display: none; } } .page-admin .devicebox {max-width: 350px;} .page-admin .devicebox .video_iframe {position: relative; height: 0; padding-bottom: 56.9%;} .page-admin .devicebox .video_iframe iframe {width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute;} /*--&gt;&lt;!]]]]]]&gt;&lt;![CDATA[&gt;&lt;![CDATA[&gt;*/ /*--&gt;&lt;!]]]]&gt;&lt;![CDATA[&gt;*/ /*--&gt;&lt;!]]&gt;*/ &lt;/style&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386669265/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/gHHsL4YMC4g" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Rich Edmonds</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb2aa24/sc/23/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Ct0Emobile0Erolling0Eout0Eupdate0Egalaxy0Es7/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save $6 on these Nexus 6P anti-glare screen protectors today!</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/YroYPtl8S7I/story01.htm</link>
      <description>Often times cases are added to protect the back and sides of a new phone, but the front is left untouched. Avoiding scratches on your Nexus 6P screen can be as easy as adding some anti-glare screen protectors to it. Today, you can grab them for just $8.95. ...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 10:00:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53414 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"><div class="field-items"><div class="field-item even"><p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/save-6-these-anti-glare-nexus-6p-screen-protectors-today' title="Save $6 on these Nexus 6P anti-glare screen protectors today!"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/w698/public/postimages/%5Buid%5D/L22751.jpg?itok=-UTw6kal' /></a></p> <p>Often times cases are added to protect the back and sides of a new phone, but the front is left untouched. Avoiding scratches on your Nexus 6P screen can be as easy as adding some <a href="http://www.shopandroid.com/tru-protection-anti-glare-screen-protectors/15A43A22751.htm?utm_campaign=community&amp;utm_source=d_ac&amp;utm_medium=content">anti-glare screen protectors</a> to it. Today, you can grab them for just $8.95.</p> </div></div></div><br clear='all'/><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/a2.htm"><img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/a2.img" border="0"/></a><img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386639137/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/a2t.img" border="0"/><img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/mf.gif' border='0'/><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/YroYPtl8S7I" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>ShopAndroid.com</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb3039f/sc/15/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Csave0E60Ethese0Eanti0Eglare0Enexus0E6p0Escreen0Eprotectors0Etoday/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Import listing hints at Moto X3 with 5-inch display</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/z5ADeOyTRTA/story01.htm</link>
      <description>Indian import export website Zauba has listed a device with the Moto X3 moniker making its way to the country. The listing shows that eight units in total were imported into the country from the U.S., likely headed for software testing and validation at Motorola's R&amp;amp;D facility in India. There's no mention of specs, but the phone is listed with a 5-inch display and single-SIM connectivity. With Lenovo restructuring its mobile division, it is likely the upcoming Moto X3 will be the first device to feature the "Moto by Lenovo" branding. Not much else is known at this stage, but the pricing of the individual units of the phone at ₹6,812 ($102) is in line considering they're meant meant for testing and not slated for retail use. We'll share more details as we receive them. Until then, what are your thoughts on the 5-inch screen size for the Moto X3? ...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 09:13:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53420 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"><div class="field-items"><div class="field-item even"><p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/import-listing-hints-moto-x3-5-inch-display' title="Import listing hints at Moto X3 with 5-inch display"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2015/09/moto-x-pure-left.jpg?itok=puN0hxfK' /></a></p> <p>Indian import export website Zauba has listed a device with the <a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./tag/moto-x3">Moto X3</a> moniker making its way to the country. The listing shows that eight units in total were imported into the country from the U.S., likely headed for software testing and validation at Motorola's R&amp;D facility in India. There's no mention of specs, but the phone is listed with a 5-inch display and single-SIM connectivity.</p> <!--break--> <p><a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/import-listing-hints-moto-x3-5-inch-display' title="Import listing hints at Moto X3 with 5-inch display"><img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large/public/article_images/2016/04/moto-x3-listing.png?itok=RstQuMbt' /></a></p> <p>With Lenovo restructuring its mobile division, it is likely the upcoming Moto X3 will be the first device to feature the "Moto by Lenovo" branding. Not much else is known at this stage, but the <a href="https://www.zauba.com/import-motorola+moto+x3/hs-code-85171290-hs-code.html">pricing</a> of the individual units of the phone at ₹6,812 ($102) is in line considering they're meant meant for testing and not slated for retail use. We'll share more details as we receive them. Until then, what are your thoughts on the 5-inch screen size for the Moto X3?</p> </div></div></div><br clear='all'/><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"><img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/></a><br/><br/><a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/a2.htm"><img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/></a><img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386638622/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/><img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/><img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/z5ADeOyTRTA" height="1" width="1" alt=""/>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Harish Jonnalagadda</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb3015f/sc/23/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Cimport0Elisting0Ehints0Emoto0Ex30E50Einch0Edisplay/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walmart is discounting the Galaxy S7 by $150</title>
      <link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/androidcentral/~3/0X7n3VyraL0/story01.htm</link>
      <description>If you're holding out for a deal on the Galaxy S7, look no further. Walmart is offering a $150 discount on Samsung's latest flagship device. The promotion is valid on all in-store purchases bought on monthly installment plans from AT&amp;amp;T, Verizon, or Sprint. If you're looking to get the device with T-Mobile, you'll have to look elsewhere. The $150 discount will be reflected as credit on your monthly invoice, according to CNN Money. The promotion itself will be available until the end of June. The retailer is also offering the same discount on last year's Galaxy S6. Who's interested in taking Walmart up on its offer? Samsung Galaxy S7 and S7 edge Galaxy S7 review Galaxy S7 edge review Galaxy S7 edge with Exynos: A Canadian perspective Here are all four Galaxy S7 colors Details on the Galaxy S7's camera The SD card is back on the GS7 Join our Galaxy S7 forums AT&amp;amp;T Sprint T-Mobile Verizon */ /*--&gt;*/ /*--&gt;*/ ...&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 05:20:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53418 at http://www.androidcentral.com</guid>
      <content:encoded>&lt;div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"&gt;&lt;div class="field-items"&gt;&lt;div class="field-item even"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href='http://www.androidcentral.com/walmart-discounting-galaxy-s7-150' title="Walmart is discounting the Galaxy S7 by $150"&gt;&lt;img src='http://www.androidcentral.com/sites/androidcentral.com/files/styles/large_wm_brw/public/article_images/2016/03/galaxy-s7-box-left.jpg?itok=JiHNDLR9' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you're holding out for a deal on the &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/samsung-galaxy-s7"&gt;Galaxy S7&lt;/a&gt;, look no further. Walmart is offering a $150 discount on Samsung's latest flagship device.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;!--break--&gt; &lt;p&gt;The promotion is valid on all in-store purchases bought on monthly installment plans from AT&amp;amp;T, Verizon, or Sprint. If you're looking to get the device with T-Mobile, you'll have to look elsewhere. The $150 discount will be reflected as credit on your monthly invoice, according to &lt;a href="http://money.cnn.com/2016/04/01/technology/walmart-iphone/index.html?iid=hp-stack-dom"&gt;&lt;em&gt;CNN Money&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The promotion itself will be available until the end of June. The retailer is also offering the same discount on last year's &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s6"&gt;Galaxy S6&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Who's interested in taking Walmart up on its offer?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="devicebox"&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s7"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S7 and S7 edge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;div class="video"&gt;&lt;div class="video_iframe"&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/wCpHEsi6NfA?rel=0&amp;amp;autoplay=0&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&amp;amp;controls=2&amp;amp;autohide=1&amp;amp;showinfo=0" width="680" height="383" class="video-filter video-youtube vf-wcphesi6nfa" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;!--/video--&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s7-review?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Galaxy S7 review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/./samsung-galaxy-s7-edge-review?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Galaxy S7 edge review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/samsung-galaxy-s7-edge-review-canadian-perspective?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Galaxy S7 edge with Exynos: A Canadian perspective&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/comparing-galaxy-s7-and-s7-edge-colors?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Here are all four Galaxy S7 colors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/galaxy-s7s-camera-drops-12mp-picks-14-micron-pixels-and-even-faster-focusing?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Details on the Galaxy S7's camera&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/galaxy-s7-regains-microsd-card-shuns-adoptable-storage?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;The SD card is back on the GS7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://forums.androidcentral.com/samsung-galaxy-s7/?utm_medium=custombox&amp;amp;utm_campaign=navigation&amp;amp;utm_source=ac"&gt;Join our Galaxy S7 forums&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/ext?link=http%3A%2F%2Fclick.linksynergy.com%2Ffs-bin%2Fclick%3Fid%3DJAF5WzpxbKM%26subid%3D%26offerid%3D321145.1%26type%3D10%26tmpid%3D13664%26u1%3Ddac%26RD_PARM1%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fwww.att.com%252Fcellphones%252Fsamsung%252Fgalaxy-s7.html" title="" class="buy-link" rel="nofollow"&gt;AT&amp;amp;T&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sprint.com/apps/new-samsung-galaxy-phone-offers/index.html" title="" class="buy-link"&gt;Sprint&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/ext?link=http%3A%2F%2Ft-mobile.7eer.net%2Fc%2F159229%2F187812%2F3290%3FsubId1%3Dd_ac%26subId2%3Dd_ac%26u%3Dhttp%253A%252F%252Fwww.t-mobile.com%252Fcell-phones%252Fsamsung-galaxy-s7.html" title="" class="buy-link" rel="nofollow"&gt;T-Mobile&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.androidcentral.com/ext?link=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.jdoqocy.com%2Fclick-7293382-11365093-1445520420000%3Fsid%3Dd_ac%26url%3Dhttp%253A%252F%252Fwww.verizonwireless.com%252Fsmartphones%252Fsamsung-galaxy-s7%252F" title="" class="buy-link" rel="nofollow"&gt;Verizon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div&gt; &lt;style&gt; &lt;!--/*--&gt;&lt;![CDATA[/* &gt;&lt;!--*/ &lt;!--/*--&gt;&lt;![CDATA[/* &gt;&lt;!--*/ &lt;!--/*--&gt;&lt;![CDATA[/* &gt;&lt;!--*/ /* ALL SIZES */ .devicebox { background: #fff; border: solid #000; border-width: 2px 0; box-sizing: border-box; margin: 0 auto 30px; overflow: auto; padding: 20px 0 15px; position: relative; } div .devicebox ul li, div .devicebox p { box-sizing: border-box; color: #000; display: table; font: 16px "Proxima Nova Th",helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; width: 100%; } .devicebox h3 { color: #000; font: 26px/0.9 "Proxima Nova Bold",helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; margin: 0 0 15px; text-transform: uppercase; } .devicebox a { color: #008099; } .devicebox .video { margin: 0 auto 15px; } .devicebox p { margin: 0px; } .devicebox p.list-head { font: 20px "Proxima Nova Bold",helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; padding: 0 15px; } .devicebox p img, .entry-content .devicebox p &gt; img { width: 100%; } .devicebox ul { display: table; margin: 0 0 10px; width: 100%; } .devicebox ul li { background: #f7f7f7; margin: 2px 0; padding: 4px 15px; } .devicebox ul li:hover { background: #fff; } .devicebox ul li:before { display: none; } .devicebox p ~ p { line-height: 1.25; } .devicebox p:first-of-type + p { padding: 15px; } .devicebox a.buy-link { border-radius: 5px; display: inline-block; font: 14px/31px "Proxima Nova Extrabld",Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; text-align: center; } .devicebox a.buy-link, .devicebox a.buy-link:link, .devicebox a.buy-link:active, .devicebox a.buy-link:visited { background: #37B5D7; color: #FFF; } .devicebox a.buy-link:hover { background: #2694B2; text-decoration: none; } .devicebox a.buy-link:before { content: "\e61e"; font: 40px/0 "ac_iconset" !important; margin: 0 3px 0 -8px; vertical-align: middle; } /* PORTRAIT */ div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) { float: right; margin: 0 0 20px 20px; max-width: 350px; width: 50%; } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox h3, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) h3 { text-align: center; } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) a.buy-link { margin: 0 5px 8px 0; width: calc(50% - 5px); } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(even), div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) .devicebox a.buy-link:last-child, div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(even), div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) .devicebox a.buy-link:last-child { margin-right: 0; } div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child { display: block; margin-right: 0; width: auto; } /* LANDSCAPE */ @media all and (min-width: 1025px) { .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox { padding: 20px 0 25px; } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox .video, .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { float: left; margin: 0 30px 0 0; width: calc(100% - 375px); } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { bottom: 20px; display: block; overflow: hidden; position: absolute; top: 59px; } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p img, .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p &gt; img { position: absolute; top: 50%; transform: translateY(-50%); } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p, .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox ul { box-sizing: border-box; margin-left: calc(100% - 345px); width: 340px; } .article-body-wrap &gt; div:not(.columns-3) &gt; *:first-child:not(.sticky-wrapper) div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p.list-head { margin-top: -5px; } } @media all and (min-width: 1025px), all and (max-width: 800px) and (min-width: 660px), all and (max-width: 500px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link { margin: 0 5px 8px 0; width: calc(50% - 5px); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(even), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:last-child { margin-right: 0; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child { display: block; width: auto; } } @media all and (max-width: 800px) and (min-width: 660px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox { padding: 20px 0 25px; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox .video, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { float: left; margin: 0 30px 0 0; width: calc(100% - 375px); } div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 + p { bottom: 20px; display: block; overflow: hidden; position: absolute; top: 59px; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p img, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p &gt; img { position: absolute; top: 50%; transform: translateY(-50%); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox ul { box-sizing: border-box; margin-left: calc(100% - 345px); width: 340px; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox p.list-head { margin-top: -5px; } } @media all and (max-width: 1024px) and (min-width: 801px), all and (max-width: 660px) and (min-width: 501px) { div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox a.buy-link:before, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) a.buy-link:before { display: none; } } @media all and (max-width: 660px), all and (max-width: 1024px) and (min-width: 801px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox h3 { text-align: center; } div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox ul, div :last-of-type ~ .devicebox p { display: block; } } @media all and (max-width: 660px) and (min-width: 501px), all and (max-width: 1024px) and (min-width: 801px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link { margin: 0 5px 8px 0; width: calc((100% / 3) - 7px); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n):nth-last-child(odd), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n):nth-last-child(n+3) { margin-right: 0; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(2), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(2) ~ a, div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(4), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(4) ~ a { width: calc(50% - 5px); } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(2) ~ a:nth-last-of-type(odd), div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-of-type(3n+1):nth-last-of-type(4) ~ a:nth-last-of-type(odd) { margin-right: 0; } div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox a.buy-link:nth-child(odd):last-child { display: inline-block; } } @media all and (max-width: 800px) { div *:last-of-type ~ .devicebox { margin: 0 0 30px; max-width: none; width: auto; } } @media all and (max-width: 500px) { .devicebox, div *:not(:last-of-type):not(div) + .devicebox, div .netshelter-ad + .devicebox:not(:nth-last-of-type(3)) { float: none; margin: 0 0 30px; max-width: none; width: auto; } .devicebox a.buy-link:before { display: none; } } .page-admin .devicebox {max-width: 350px;} .page-admin .devicebox .video_iframe {position: relative; height: 0; padding-bottom: 56.9%;} .page-admin .devicebox .video_iframe iframe {width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute;} /*--&gt;&lt;!]]]]]]&gt;&lt;![CDATA[&gt;&lt;![CDATA[&gt;*/ /*--&gt;&lt;!]]]]&gt;&lt;![CDATA[&gt;*/ /*--&gt;&lt;!]]&gt;*/ &lt;/style&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br clear='all'/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/rc/1/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/rc/1/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/rc/2/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/rc/2/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/rc/3/rc.htm" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rc.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/rc/3/rc.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/a2.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://da.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/a2.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img width="1" height="1" src="http://pi.feedsportal.com/r/247386665662/u/49/f/616884/c/33995/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/a2t.img" border="0"/&gt;&lt;img width='1' height='1' src='http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/mf.gif' border='0'/&gt;&lt;img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/androidcentral/~4/0X7n3VyraL0" height="1" width="1" alt=""/&gt;</content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Harish Jonnalagadda</dc:creator>
      <feedburner:origLink>http://androidcentral.com.feedsportal.com/c/33995/f/616884/s/4eb29aac/sc/23/l/0L0Sandroidcentral0N0Cwalmart0Ediscounting0Egalaxy0Es70E150A/story01.htm</feedburner:origLink>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
